<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<products type="array">
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic &lt;b&gt;amarone&lt;/b&gt; with a nose of berry fruits with nuances of vanilla and chocolate. On the palate, it is structured, classy and elegant, silky. Strong, rich and vigorous, yet surprising balanced.</description>
    <name>Amarone della Valpolicella Classico 2000, Valetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An extraordinary &lt;b&gt;merlot&lt;/b&gt;, single vineyards, made from 100% &lt;b&gt;merlot&lt;/b&gt; grapes from very old vines located in Piedmont, in the heart of the Barolo area, &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in small French barrels. This &lt;b&gt;merlot&lt;/b&gt; has a great structure, is elegant, full bodied, harmoniums, with a nose of rose, chocolate and red fruits and a lick of vanilla from small French barrels. It has a lingering aftertaste with sweet tannins. This wine is only produced in 1000 bottles per vintage and in the best vintages</description>
    <name>Merlot Armire', Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A very elegant &lt;b&gt;barbaresco&lt;/b&gt; made with 100% hand picked Nebbiolo grapes from vineyards surrounding the town of Barbaresco. This &lt;b&gt;barbaresco&lt;/b&gt;, from a fantastic vintage, shows an impenetrable garnet colour and aromas of roses and violets with underlying scents of vanilla and liquorice. On the palate, is classy and elegant, round and very smooth with a lingering aftertaste.</description>
    <name>Barbaresco 2000, Rivetto</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This &lt;b&gt;Barbera d'Alba Superiore&lt;/b&gt;, obtained from 100% &lt;b&gt;barbera&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards surrounding the town of Alba, is a full bodied red wine with aromas of ripe fruit and scents of vanilla. It is well balanced, soft, sharmonic and with a lingering aftertaste.</description>
    <name>Barbera d'Alba Superiore, Rivetto</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Whole char-grilled roasted artichokes. Excellent as a pannini filling or side salad.          </description>
    <name>Whole char-grilled artichokes in vegetable oil  (Gr 650)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Mixed mushrooms in vegetable oil.     </description>
    <name>Mixed mushrooms in vegetable oil (Gr 650)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Aubergines in vegetable oil. </description>
    <name>Aubergines in vegetable oil (Gr 650)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic Sauvignon from Friuli, north east of Italy, from the Colli Orientali area made with 100% manually harvested sauvignon grapes from old vines, with an aromatic and delicate nose with scents of yellow pepper, peach and sage. Full, elegant with fruity flavours and a never ending finish. Another masterpiece from Scubla
</description>
    <name>Sauvignon Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The hamper contains a stunning collection of Italian tastes and includes a large range of sweet and savoury delicacies presented in an elegantly gift wrapped wood basket. It makes a fantastic gift suitable for any occasion. The hamper contains: 

&amp;#149;	1 handmade Panettone nicely wrapped 750gr
&amp;#149;	1 box of biscuits or sweeties
&amp;#149;	1 bottle of Bardolino Chiaretto (rose&amp;rsquo;) 
&amp;#149;	1 bottle of Merlot
&amp;#149;	1 bottle of Pinot grigio
&amp;#149;	1 bottle of dessert wine
&amp;#149;	2 bottle of prosecco
&amp;#149;	1 bottle of extra virgin olive oil cold pressed
&amp;#149;	A selection of 2 pasta sauces
&amp;#149;	A selection of 3 Italian specialties in extra virgin olive oil

</description>
    <name>"Christmas in Italy" hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The name 40/60 indicates the percentage of grapes that makes this red wine from Latium, 40% &lt;b&gt;syrah&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;shiraz&lt;/b&gt; and 60% &lt;b&gt;Cesanese&lt;/b&gt;, a native grape that produces outstanding wines, aged for 6 months in barrels. This full bodied, rich and well rounded red wine, shows aromas of black fruits and a lick of vanilla, and on the palate is full, round and with an elegant finish. This red wine is suitable for vegan</description>
    <name>40/60 Organic L'Olivella</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A red wine made with 100% &lt;b&gt;Aleatico&lt;/b&gt; grapes, intensely aromatic, with aromas of roses and ripe blackberries. Rich, medium sweet and with a good acidity. A very powerful red wine, it stands up well to very mature, strongly flavoured cheeses, dry pastries, almond and chestnut paste and roasted almonds.</description>
    <name>Aleatico di Puglia IGT, Cantine Botta</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Panettone is for Italians the classic Christmas cake. There cannot be be Christmas without eating panettone or pandoro and drinking spumante. This Panettone with dried grapes, has been made using only natural ingredients, without preservatives or additives and hand wrapped. Experience the real taste of the panettone with Antica Pasticceria Betti. To enjoy the panettone at its best, heat the slice in the oven for a few minutes and let the fragrances invade the kitchen</description>
    <name>Handmade panettone tradizionale, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Amarone, another fantastic Italian red wine, from the Veneto Region. Made using Corvina, Corvinone and Rondinella grapes following the ripasso method, this wine is strong, rich and vigorous in the mouth, yet surprising in its balance, maturity and refinement. 
</description>
    <name>Amarone, Valetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Mixed vegetables in vegetal oil.</description>
    <name>Antipasto mediterraneo in vegetable oil Gr 650)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Freshly-picked Italian &lt;b&gt;asparagus&lt;/b&gt;, with a very delicate taste, in olive oil ideal to compliment a main course or to be used in the preparation of more elaborated dishes. The fresh &lt;b&gt;asparagus&lt;/b&gt; are immediately put in olive oil to preserve their full flavour. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Asparagus, Triveri </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This pate, made with freshly picked and cut Italian &lt;b&gt;asparagus&lt;/b&gt; minced and then puy in olive oil, has a very delicate taste and is ideal to spread over bruschettas or to use as an ingredient for pasta. For ideas, visit our recipes section</description>
    <name>Asparagus pate', Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Aubergines  pasta tomatoes sauce.</description>
    <name>Aubergines and tomatoes pasta sauce      (4 people)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Freshly-picked Italian &lt;b&gt;aubergines&lt;/b&gt;, cut into slices and then put in olive oil, ideal as an antipast or to complement an aperitiv but can also be used as an ingredient in the preparation of more elaborated dishes. For ideas visit our recipes section.
</description>
    <name>Aubergines, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This &lt;b&gt;Modena Balsamic vinegar&lt;/b&gt; has been aged for at least 10 years in traditional barrels. It is very thick, smooth and rich with a slight sweetness. Excellent on salads, pasta, pizza, bread and to flavor sauces. Also used on ice cream, dessert and to make cocktails.</description>
    <name>Modena Balsamic vinegar aged 10 years</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This high quality &lt;b&gt;Traditional Modena Balsamic Vinegar&lt;/b&gt; in a 250ml gift bottle has been aged for at least 7 years in traditional barrels. It is dense, rich, complex and with a slight sweetness. Excellent on salads, pasta, pizza, bread and to flavor sauces. Also used on ice cream, dessert and to make cocktails
</description>
    <name>Modena Balsamic vinegar aged 7 years</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This high quality Modena Balsamic Vinegar has been aged for at least 3 years in traditional barrels. It is smooth and rich with a slight sweetness. Excellent on salads, pasta, pizza, bread and to flavor sauces. Also used on ice cream, dessert and to make cocktails.</description>
    <name>Modena Balsamic vinegar aged 3 years</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made from grapes grown in vineyards planted along the Lake of Garda, surrounding the town of Bardolino, is light and easy to drink. It has a lively bouquet, with scents of red fruit with hints of strawberries and red cherries. On the palate is light, fruity and with a pleasant touch of acidity that leaves a clean finish. It is a fantastic value for money Bardolino</description>
    <name>Bardolino Classico, Valetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Pio Cesare is one of the wine making masters in Piedmont. This Barolo, from a very good vintage, and kept in the cellar at the right temperature and humidity, is one of the very last few bottles left. This Barolo has an intense and deep, almost impenetrable, colour, bursting with aromas of rose and violet. The palate is velvety and rich, showing good structure and a lasting finish. The Barolo &amp;ldquo;Ornato&amp;rdquo; is more modern in style than the classic Barolo, but still true to its roots. </description>
    <name>Barolo Ornato 1993 Pio Cesare</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This &lt;b&gt;Barolo Cerequio 2001&lt;/b&gt;, made with Nebbiolo grapes from old vines of a single vineyard, called Cerequio, with a very low yield in the heart of the Barolo area, in La Morra, is one of the best expressions. Produced only in thousand bottles per year, these are sold well before being bottled. This 2001 vintage, a very good vintage for &lt;b&gt;barolo&lt;/b&gt; wines, has an intense garnet colour, with aromas of black currant and red fruits with an underlying hints of vanilla. Elegant, well balanced, full bodied and complex with an enduring aftertaste and amazing sweet tannins. This wine has won several national and international awards including the Bronze medal at the International wine challenge</description>
    <name>Barolo Cerequio 2001, Giacomo Marengo </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Barolo Giulin 2004 from the Rivetto Family is an extremely clean and fresh wine, with tar and berry aromas that follows through to a full-bodied palate. Plenty of tannins and lots of acidity, it needs time. Decanter Best value Barolo 2004 </description>
    <name>Barolo Giulin 2004, Rivetto </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This &lt;b&gt;barolo&lt;/b&gt;, made with Nebbiolo grapes from old vines of a single vineyard, called Fontanazza, and a very low yield in the heart of the Barolo area, in La Morra, is another great expression of the terroir and the ability of Giacomo Marengo in making fantastic wines. Produced only in thousand bottles per year, these are sold well before being bottled. This 2001 vintage, a very good vintage for &lt;b&gt;barolo&lt;/b&gt;, is elegant and classy, with an intense garnet colour and perfumes of raspberry, dried flowers and berries. On the palate, is full, rich, complex and well balanced with silky tannins and a long caressing finish. This Barolo has won several national and international awards including the Bronze medal at the International wine challenge.</description>
    <name>Barolo Fontanazza 2001, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A masterpiece. A premium lightly oaked, rich, white wine from Friuli. A blend of &lt;b&gt;Chardonnay&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Tocai Friulano&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Reisling Renano&lt;/b&gt;, fermented and refined in barriques, elegant and rich,, aromatic with aromas of fruits underlying hints of vanilla and with an enduring aftertaste in the mouth. This wine has won several Italian and international awards, including the 3 glasses from the Gambero Rosso which is the maximum score an Italian wine can be given. The wine was named after the famous refuge in the Alps. Roberto and a friend were caught by a storm when descending the Alps and during the wait, they shaped the wine.</description>
    <name>Bianco Pomedes Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A masterpiece. A premium lightly oaked, rich, white wine from Friuli. A blend of &lt;b&gt;Chardonnay&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Tocai Friulano&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Reisling Renano&lt;/b&gt;, fermented and refined in barriques, elegant and rich,, aromatic with aromas of fruits underlying hints of vanilla and with an enduring aftertaste in the mouth. This wine has won several Italian and international awards, including the 3 glasses from the Gambero Rosso which is the maximum score an Italian wine can be given. The wine was named after the famous refuge in the Alps. Roberto and a friend were caught by a storm when descending the Alps and during the wait, they shaped the wine. This magnum is the perfect gift idea for a wine lover</description>
    <name>Bianco Pomedes Magnum, Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Italian &lt;b&gt;black olives&lt;/b&gt; pate in olive oil ideal for bruschetta or as an ingredient for the preparation of more elaborated dishes. For ideas, visit our recipes section  
</description>
    <name>Black olives pate, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Italian &lt;b&gt;black olives&lt;/b&gt; marinated in olive oil and peppers, ideal as an aperitif, to accompany a glass of prosecco or white wine or as an ingredient in the preparation of more elaborated dishes. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Black olives, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The 1997 has been a fantastic vintage for Tuscany, the vintage has been given 5 stars, and this &lt;b&gt;Brunello di Montalcino&lt;/b&gt; it&amp;rsquo;s possibly its maximum expression. Made only from selected grapes from a single vineyard, this &lt;b&gt;Brunello di Montalcino&lt;/b&gt; has a lively garnet colour and an intense aroma with scents of aromatics woods, small fruits and a lick of vanilla. On the mouth, the wine has an elegant and harmonic body with strength and breeding. &lt;b&gt;Brunello di Montalcino&lt;/b&gt; improves with ageing and can be kept for more than 30 years, especially the best vintages</description>
    <name>Brunello di Montalcino Vigna degli Angeli 1997, La Gerla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The 1997 has been a superlative vintage for Tuscany, it has been awarded 5 stars, and this &lt;b&gt;Brunello di Montalcino&lt;/b&gt; it&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic expression. Made only from selected grapes, this &lt;b&gt;Brunello di Montalcino&lt;/b&gt; has a lively garnet colour and an intense aroma with scents of aromatics woods, small fruits and jams. On the mouth, the wine has an elegant and harmonic body with strength and breeding. &lt;b&gt;Brunello di Montalcino&lt;/b&gt; improves with ageing and can be kept for more than 30 years, especially the best vintages. </description>
    <name>Brunello di Montalcino 1997, La Gerla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Handmade brutti ma buoni, ugly but tasty, this is what the name mean, and we definitely agree. The 'tasty' refers to the heart of almonds, soft and crunchy, and the 'ugly' refers to their uneven shape in a Christmas themed box. Another Tuscan classic. These biscuits are made with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients.  BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</description>
    <name>Handmade brutti ma buoni, Antica Pasticceria Betti BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Build your hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with 100% &lt;b&gt;cabernet franc&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards located in Friuli, in the Colli Orientali area, this characterful red wine, with its distinctive herbaceous, rustic and penetrating raspberry aroma that as the wine matures evolve into a complex sweet-smelling fragrance   </description>
    <name>Cabernet Franc Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made from 100% &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Franc&lt;/b&gt; grown in vineyards located in Friuli, too often used in blend including Bordeaux and very few times on its own, this red wine has an intense red colour, inimitable herby aroma, almost of just cut hay, which can seem aggressive when young but then it grows aristocratic and complete with time 
</description>
    <name>Cabernet Franc,  Montalbano</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with 100% &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon&lt;/b&gt; grapes, this wine has an intense ruby red colour, a slightly spicy aroma with a lick of vanilla and a well balanced, round and smooth on the palate. </description>
    <name>Cabernet Sauvignon Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A white wine made with a red grape that is a revelation. From vineyards located in one of the most prolific area of Sardinia for the &lt;b&gt;cannonau&lt;/b&gt; grape, this wine is a refreshing and elegant dry white wine, with a delicate nose and a full palate with nutty and honeyed characters.</description>
    <name>Calaluna White Cannonau, Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A full bodied &lt;b&gt;cannonau&lt;/b&gt; wine bursting with aromas of ripe fruit and plums. Round, soft and very smooth on the palate. This wine is made with 100% &lt;b&gt;cannonau&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards situated in one of the most prolific area of Sardinia for this grape. </description>
    <name>Cannonau di Sardegna DOC Filieri Rosso, Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic &lt;b&gt;cannonau di Sardegna riserva&lt;/b&gt;, elegant and classy, warm and well balanced, a classic Sardinian red wine. Made only from the best &lt;b&gt;cannonau&lt;/b&gt; grapes from very old vines from a single vineyard, matured and aged in small barrels, this wine is bursting with aromas of violets and blackberry with underlying hints of vanilla. In the mouth is full, silky and with soft tannins. It is recommended to decant the wine before opening. </description>
    <name>Cannonau di Sardegna Riserva , Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This &lt;b&gt;cannonau&lt;/b&gt;, voted by the Gambero Rosso as the best value for money Italian wines for the 2008, is made from grapes harvested from a single vineyard, Vigna di Isalle, and shows aromas of fruits and spices, it is well structured and elegant on the palate and with a lasting aftertaste. </description>
    <name>Cannonau di Sardegna DOC Vigna di Isalle, Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The classic version of probably the most famous biscuits in the world, the Cantuccini, these crunchy, handmade biscuits with whole almonds are full of flavour and, according to the tradition, are sipped into the Vin Santo after the meal. They are also often offered together with coffees or cappuccinos.  These cantuccini biscuits are made only using natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients.</description>
    <name>Traditional Cantuccini</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Whole artichokes hearts in extra-virgin olive oil,perfect as an antipasto or salad starter. </description>
    <name>Carciofini in olio extravergine d&amp;rsquo;oliva (280g)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A dark, full bodied, organic rose&amp;rsquo; wine made from 100% &lt;b&gt;montepulciano&lt;/b&gt; grapes, with a fruit driven nose, with scents of cherry and red fruit. On the palate is elegant and with an enduring aftertaste</description>
    <name>Cerasuolo d Abruzzo Organic D.O.C.Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A rich, full bodied, organic &lt;b&gt;chardonnay&lt;/b&gt; bursting with aromas of tropical fruits. On the mouth, this wine is refreshing and crispy, ideal for warm summer days</description>
    <name>Chardonnay, Organic Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Chenti is a blend of organically grown grapes of Refosco del Peduncolo rosso, a native grape from Friuli, and Cabernet Franc, aged in small barrels for 6/8 months to enrich and add structure to the wine. This wine is elegant, classy, medium bodied with aromas of ripe fruits and spices and underlying hints of vanilla. In the mouth is smooth, warm, with fruity flavours and a lasting aftertaste. </description>
    <name>Chenti,Organic Montalbano</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A refreshing and crispy chardonnay from Tuscany. Made only with the best grapes from vineyards surrounding the ancient town of Cortona, this white wine shows aromas of citrus combined with more mature fruit, peach and pear. In the mouth is light, refreshing and with a lovely acidity and long end.
</description>
    <name>Chardonnay IGT Tuscany, Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A wonderful Chianti Classico Riserva ready to be enjoyed. A wonderful red wine, elegant, rich with a full palate and a spicy nose with scents of vanilla.The finish is long and gives a fine, delicate aftertaste.
</description>
    <name>Chianti Classico Riserva 2000, San Pietro in Avenano</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Chianti, one of the most famous Italian red wines in its organic version. Produced from grapes obtained from vineyards located between Siena and Arezzo grown organically, in San Savino, this organic Chianti Colli Aretini is made only using the best grapes of Sangiovese and a small percentage of Cabernet Sauvignon. The result is Chianti Colli Aretini with character, a fresh wine with a good intensity, a nice ruby colour and a nose of mature red fruits with a good structure and a light tannin.</description>
    <name>Chianti DOCG Castello di Rapale Organic, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A full bodied, classic and rich &lt;b&gt;Chianti Colli Aretini&lt;/b&gt;, with an intense bouquet of mature red fruits and spices and a long ending, as a &lt;b&gt;Chianti&lt;/b&gt; should be</description>
    <name>Chianti DOCG Le Tornaie, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An outstanding, unmistakably &lt;b&gt;Chianti Riserva&lt;/b&gt;, plury awararded, winner of a &lt;b&gt;Decanter Gold medal winner&lt;/b&gt; and included by the Observer amongst the &lt;b&gt;50 best wines of 2006&lt;/b&gt;. This elegant, classy, full bodied and balanced &lt;b&gt;Chianti Riserva&lt;/b&gt;, shows aromas of black cherry with hints of vanilla. On the mouth, it has a wonderful structure and great tannic tenderness. Produced in limited quantity</description>
    <name>Chianti Riserva DOCG 1999 La Commenda, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>If you think your food is not "hot" enough, try these Italian chilli pepper, made with the freshest chilli peppers conserved in extra virgin olive oil. The chilli peppers are immediately put in extra virgin olive oil to preserve their flavour</description>
    <name>Chilli Peppers, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Fromt the wine to compliment to your turkey to the bubble wine, the case contains all you need to celebrate. 
The case contains the following award winning wines:
2 Prosecco 
2 Pinot Grigio
2 Frascati
2 Merlot Rose
2 Chianti 
2 Chianti Riserva 1999   (included by The Observer amongst the 50 best wines of 2006)

Save &amp;pound;8.49 on the normal price

</description>
    <name>Christmas Case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Like the city to which the hamper is named after, this is the ultimate Christmas luxury hamper, in a pretty willow basket, guaranteed to make your gift standing out. It contains the finest selection of Italian food and wine:

Handmade Cantuccini 300gr
Artichokes in extra virgin olive oil 280gr
Modena Balsamic Vinegar aged 10 years 250ml
Black olives in extra virgin olive oil 280gr
Cesanese (Organic red wine) 75cl
In Privio Extra virgin olive oil from Umbria 500ml
Vermentino di Sardegna 75cl
Pinot Chardonnay Spumante 75cl
Chianti Riserva La Commenda 2000 75cl
Filieri Rosato 75cl
Organic pasta 250gr
Handmade Panforte 500gr
Box of chocolate
Handmade Panettone 1KG
</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper "Venice"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Like Florence, this elegant Christmas hamper includes something for every member of the family, from the cantuccini for the little ones to a fantastic Chianti Riserva 2000 for the big ones. The hamper contains:

Chianti Riserva La Commenda 2000 75cl
Handmade Panettone 1KG
Artichokes in extra virgin olive oil 250gr
Black olives in extra virgin olive oil 250gr
Handmade Cantuccini 300gr
Box of chocolate
Organic pasta 250gr
Pasta sauce (4 portions)
Colleruita DOP Extra virgin olive oil from Umbria 250ml
Pinot Grigio Dal Cero 75cl
Vin Santo 1995 La Casaccia 375ml
Pinot Chardonnay Spumante 75cl
</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper "Florence"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The essential Christmas hamper to celebrate Christmas the Italian way with plenty of wine and food for the whole family. The hamper contains:

Handmade Panettone 1KG
Pinot Chardonnay Spumante 75cl
Handmade Cantuccini 300gr
Black olives in extra virgin olive oil 250gr
Pinot Grigio Dal Cero 75cl
Selverello Dal Cero 75cl
Modena Balsamic Vinegar aged 3 years 250cl
</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper  "Naples"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The hamper contains the folliwing products: Panettone exotic fruits 750gr, Extra virgin olive oil 75cl, Biscotti, 1 box of pasta, 1 chilli pepper in extra virgin olive oil, 2 aromatic extra virgin olive oil, Pasta sauce, 2 boxes of risotto.</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper  4</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Our Christmas hamper contains: 1 Panettone exotic fruits 750gr, a bag of cantuccini with apricots, , 2 box of organic pasta, 1 pasta sauces, 1 preserve in extra virgin olive oil, 1 Modena balsamic vinergar, 1 bottle of extra virgin olive oil (750cl) from Tuscany. </description>
    <name>Christmas Hampers 5</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Our Christmas hamper contains: 1 Panettone exotic fruits 750gr, a bag of cantuccini with apricots, , 2 box of organic pasta, 1 pasta sauces, 1 preserve in extra virgin olive oil, 1 Modena balsamic vinergar, 1 bottle of extra virgin olive oil (750cl) from Tuscany. </description>
    <name>Christmas Hampers    6</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic value dry white wine from Latium. Made with a blend of native grapes from vineyards surrounding the city of Rome, this dry white wine is slightly aromatic with floral aromas and an  enduring aftertaste. This white wine is suitable for vegans</description>
    <name>Colli Albani Superiore DOC, Donnardea</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These Italian artichokes, freshly-picked, cooked and minced, in olive oil have a very delicate taste and they are ideal for bruschettas or as an ingredient for pasta or main courses. The artichokes, after being minced, are immediately put in olive oil to preserve their full flavour. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Artichokes pate, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Capsicum  sauce made with organically grown bell peppers, extra-virgin olive oil, 
salt, wine vinegar, garlic and parsley.
</description>
    <name>Crema di peperoni (190g)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A bright pink, fruit driven rose&amp;rsquo; wine made with 100% merlot grapes. An easy to drink, refreshing and versatile Merlot ros&amp;egrave; for all occasions. With a fruity nose with notes of cherries and red berries, in the mouth is light, refreshing with plenty of fruity flavour and a never ending finish. It can be drunk on its own or compliment starters and light courses 
</description>
    <name>Cuvee di Merlot Rose', La braghina</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A blend of selected grapes of &lt;b&gt;Sauvignon Blanc&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Chardonnay&lt;/b&gt;, fermented separately and then &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in small French barrels. The result is a full bodied white wine, with an intense nose of tropical fruits, pineapple and banana, and underlying hints of vanilla. On the mouth, this white wine is round, soft and extremely pleasant</description>
    <name>Cuvee Sant Anna, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Dacis is a blend of organically grown grapes of &lt;b&gt;Chardonnay&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Sauvignon&lt;/b&gt; from vineyards located in Friuli, &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in small barrels for 6/8 months to enrich the wine. This wine is elegant, classy, medium bodied with scents of pear, pineapple and pistachio and a lick of vanilla. Winner of a bronze medal at the Decanter world wine awards</description>
    <name>Dacis, Organic Montalbano</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This decanter is the must have accessory for all wine lovers. Necessary for all aged wines, allow wine to breath and open itself which otehrwise, without oxigenation, will result unpleasant to drink.  </description>
    <name>Wine decanter</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Sunday Hamper has been designed to provide everything you need for a special day. A basket full of mouth watering Italian food and wine to send to friends, relatives, employees and customers all year round. All our hampers come wrapped and with a personalised card.
The hamper contains: 
1 Modena balsamic vinegar aged 5 years 
1 bottle of Extra virgin olive oil from Liguria 500cl 
1 black olives in extra virgin olive oil 280gr
1 bottle of Selverello, Dal Cero
1 bottle of Pinot Grigio, Dal Cero 
1 artichokes in extra virgin olive oil 280gr 
1 pasta sauce

For more information about our award winning Corporate hampers, please give us a call on 0191 565 4884
</description>
    <name>Sunday Hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Dolcetto d&amp;rsquo;Alba in Piedmont is considered the every day wine, easy drinking and versatile, to be enjoyed with a pizza or a more demanding dish and should be consumed young. This Dolcetto d&amp;rsquo;Alba, made from 100% Dolcetto grapes from vineyards surrounding the town of Alba, is elegant, has a bursting nose of fruits with scents of cherry. On the mouth, is smooth, soft and well balanced.</description>
    <name>Dolcetto d'Alba DOC Frach, Rivetto</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another fantastic value red wine from Donnardea made with &lt;b&gt;Sangiovese&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Merlot&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Cesanese&lt;/b&gt; grapes, medium bodied, round, soft and very smooth on the palate with floral aromas and scents of roses. Wine for all courses. Suitable for vegan
</description>
    <name>Lazio Rosso IGT Donnardea</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with 100% syrah, the New World name for Shiraz, grown in vineyards located just outside Rome, this red wine has an intense but delicate, elegant nose showing aromas of cherry, cocoa and liquorice with hints of white pepper. In the palate is light, exuberant and generous, well balanced and with a lasting ending, it is suitable for vegan 
</description>
    <name>Syrah Donnardea</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A masterpiece, a fantastic Supertuscany made with &lt;b&gt;Sangiovese&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Merlot&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in small barrique. Made using only the best grapes from 50 year old vineyards, this red wine has an intense deep ruby red colour and a complex nose bursting aromas of currants, mature plum, red fruit and underlying hints of vanilla with a well balanced, complex and lasting taste with sweet and well integrated tannins</description>
    <name>Elena, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Produced from grapes obtained from vineyards located between Siena and Arezzo grown organically, in San Savino, this red wine is made only using the best grapes of Sangiovese and Merlot from 50 years old vineyards. Belonging to the Supertuscany&amp;rsquo;s category, this red wine has an intense deep ruby red color and a nose of currants, mature plum, red fruits and vanilla with a well balanced, complex and persistent, taste and sweet and well integrated tannins. One of our favourites. This wine in its magnum version, is also an ideal present for an Italian wine lover.</description>
    <name>Elena, Marengo Magnum</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>&lt;br&gt;Choose this option if you'd like to receive our Italian wines of the month (two bottles, you can choose the composition) on your doorstep every month for only &amp;pound;180, &amp;pound;15 per month, including tasting notes and information about the producers. To cancel the membership, simply send us an email, and we will refund the membership not yet used. Joining the wine club will also entitle to a 25% discount on our wine tastings and 10% discount on your purchases from Italyabroad.com. This is the easiest to way to discover and learn about Italian wines with the help of specialists. </description>
    <name>Wine Club 2-per-Month</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>&lt;br&gt;Choose this option if you'd like to receive our Italian wines of the month (six bottles, you can choose the composition) on your doorstep every month including tasting notes and information about the producers. To cancel the membership, simply send us an email, and we will refund the membership not yet used. Joining the wine club will also entitle to a 25% discount on our wine tastings and 10% discount on your purchases from Italyabroad.com. This is the easiest to way to discover and learn about Italian wines with the help of the experts. </description>
    <name>Wine Club 6-per-Month</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An elegant, medium bodied, salmon coloured rose&amp;rsquo; made with selected &lt;b&gt;cannonau&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards located in one of the most prolific area for this grape from the Cantina di Dorgali, this versatile rose&amp;rsquo; wine has a delicate and inviting fruity bouquet and an enduring aftertaste.</description>
    <name>Cannonau rose' Filieri Rosato Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with selected Malvasia and Trebbiano grapes, this elegant, rich, traditional &lt;b&gt;frascati superiore&lt;/b&gt; is lightly honeyed on the nose with herbal hints. This wine is suitable for vegans</description>
    <name>Frascati Superiore Donnardea</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A rich and concentrate, elegant, this &lt;b&gt;Frascati superiore&lt;/b&gt; has a nose of hazelnuts and flowers and textured in the mouth. This is the wine that will make you changing your mind, that will make Frascati to become one of your favourite. Made from organically grown Malvasia grapes, this &lt;b&gt;Frascati&lt;/b&gt; is suitable for vegans </description>
    <name>Frascati Superiore Organic l'Olivella</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A classy, elegant red wine, smooth and well balanced. Made only with the best grapes of &lt;b&gt;Cannonau&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Merlot&lt;/b&gt; from vineyards located in the heart of Sardinia from Cantina di Dorgali and &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in small barriques for 12/14 months, this full bodied red wine, has a complex floral bouquet with underlying hints of vanilla and an enduring aftertaste. It is the perfect complement to rich dishes</description>
    <name>Fuili, Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This white dessert wine, obtained from &lt;b&gt;Malvasia&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Cortese&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards located along the Lake of Garda, left drying for 3 months, also called passito, is a wine rich of emotions, truly sun drops to drink like the name says. This dessert wine has a rich, fruity bouquet with licks of vanilla. On the mouth is silky and with lasting aftertaste</description>
    <name>Gocce di Sole, Valetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The gourmet hamper has been designed for the truly expert of food and wine. Offering only the finest produce, it is the gift that will make any food and wine lover happy and maybe sharing with you some of the content of the hamper... Our Gourmet hamper is a basket full of mouth watering Italian treats, from our Balsamic Vinegar aged 10 years to our Chianti Riserva 1999 which has been included by the Observer amongst the 50 best wines of 2006 or our Vin Santo 1995 and the artisan made cantuccini to sip in it. 
A basket full of mouth watering Italian food and wine to send to friends, relatives, employees and customers all year round. All our hampers come wrapped and with a personalised card. This hamper is a fantastic and original Christmas gift.
The hamper contains: 
1 box of cantuccini classici 200gr 
1 Modena balsamic vinegar aged 10 years 
1 bottle of Umbrian DOP extra virgin olive oil Colleruita Viola 500cl 
1 black olives in extra virgin olive oil 280gr
1 Chianti Riserva 1999 La Commenda, Marengo 
1 Spumante Dal Cero 
1 artichokes in extra virgin olive oil 280gr 
1 extra virgin olive oil flavoured white truffle 250ml
1 porcini mushroom in extra virgin olive oil 280gr
1 Vin Santo 1995 La Casaccia 375ml
1 Prosecco di Valdobbiadene
1 Pinot Grigio Organic
For more information about our Corporate hampers, please give us a call on 0191 565 4884. </description>
    <name>Gourmet Hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>We have chosen 12, secret, wines, a selection of red, white and rose', and we are offering you the chance to buy with up to 50% discount on the normal price, all you have to do is enjoy them, this is a great way to try different and unusual wines. You are guaranteed to win, you get the Italyabroad.com quality assured, they are good, listed wines, simply at bargain price. We also included a number of super fine wines, barolos, brunellos and many more and if you are lucky enough, you could end up with a case worth much more that what you paid for</description>
    <name>Italyabroad.com mystery case - SAVE 50%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Our special cellar includes: Barbaresco, Barolo, Amarone della Valpolicella, Barolo, Barbera d'Asti, Barbera d'Alba, Brunello di Montalcino. For more information please call us on 0191.2462032.

A wine for every occasion</description>
    <name>Italyabroad.com special cellar</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This organic &lt;b&gt;Riesling&lt;/b&gt; has a pale straw yellow colour, with an attractive, complex bouquet with floral and tropical aromas, pleasant, dry and soft in the mouth with an extra bit of weight that you would expect from grapes grown in a hotter and sunnier climate </description>
    <name>Riesling Organic Jasci e Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic rose' wine made with hand picked grapes of &lt;b&gt;Cesanese&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Sangiovese&lt;/b&gt;. To retain all the grapes characteristics, the wine has not been filtered and this make it slightly cloudy, and the results are fantastic. This salmon coloured rose&amp;rsquo; wine is refreshing and elegant and has a fruity nose and a lingering aftertaste. This rose&amp;rsquo; wine is suitable for vegans</description>
    <name>Lazio Rosato Donnardea</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An unusual grape and wine for the Italians, however, La Braghina succeeds in making this very interesting wine. This wine is medium bodied and slightly tannin. One of this six grapes allowed in the Bordeaux wines, it was until recently, rarely vinified on its own. With arrival of the new world, especially Argentina, the wine and grape have become widely known. This Malbech has a fruity nose with blackfruits, mainly blackberry, and raisins. With ageing the tannins soften and the wine become velvety. It is fruity in the motuh with a long ending.</description>
    <name>Malbech La Braghina</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An elegant, classy wine made from 100% &lt;b&gt;merlot&lt;/b&gt; grapes from a very low yielding vines &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in French oak for 12 months, this wine bursts with roses and tobacco aromas and underlying hints of vanilla. It is harmonic in the mouth, elegant and with a lingering aftertaste</description>
    <name>Merlot Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Our award winning team has put together a mixed case of red wines to introduce you to the wonderful world of Italian red wines. The wines chosen come from different regions and are of different style all made by passionate producers. The selection varies from a light bodied sangiovese from Tuscany to a full bodied and rich Syrah-Nero d'Avola from Sicily. The case includes wines to suit all tastes and for every occasion
The case contains:
2 Chenti(Friuli, Organic)
Medium bodied, made with a blend of Cabernet Franc and Refosco del Peduncolo rosso,with scents of spices and ripe cherries.
2 Refosco del Peduncolo rosso (Veneto)
Typical of the north east of Italy, has a ruby red colour, very good structure and a nose of red fruits.
2 Selverello(Tuscany)
Light, made with Sangiovese grapes, has a delicate nose, balanced wine. 
2 Dolcetto(Piedmont)
Medium bodied and with a rich bouquet of mature red fruits. 
2 Preziosaterra(Tuscany)
Made with Sangiovese, Merlot and Cabernet Sauvignon grapes, slightly oaked with a nose of mature fruits and a spicy note. 
2 Cannonau (Sardinia)
Full bodied, bursting with aromas of ripe fruit and plums. Round, soft and very smooth on the palate</description>
    <name>Italian mixed red case - SAVE 15%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From the area that produces the best pinot grigio, il Collio in Friuli, North East of Italy, only using 100% organically grown pinot grigio grapes, this white wine has a delicate floral and white fruits bouquet, with a clean, fresh and vibrant palate and a superb acidic balance, ending with a lasting, elegant, bitterly finish
</description>
    <name>Pinot Grigio Collio Organic, Coceani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From the north east of Italy, Friuli Venezia Giulia, from vineyards in the area called Colli Orientali del Friuli, obtained grapes organically grown, Montalbano makes this fantastic organic Sauvignon. This white wine has a light yellow colour with golden reflections and scents of sage, pepper and slightly herby elder. In the mouth, it is well structured and with an excellent balance fragrance-taste.</description>
    <name>Sauvignon Organic, Montalbano</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Montalcino Selection</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A classic Italian wine, powerful, complex, a full bodied red wine obtained from hand picked, selected, organically grown &lt;b&gt;Montepulciano&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards located in Abruzzo and aged for 6 months in oak barrels to give a subtle, well balanced richness. Bursting with aromas of black fruit, chocolate and scents of vanilla, this wine has fine tannins and a fruity, lasting finish</description>
    <name>Montepulciano d Abruzzo Organic, Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Jasci &amp; Marchesani is a family run estate with vineyards in Abruzzo along the Adriatic cost and has been growing grapes organically since 1978. With vineyards located between the Apennines and the sea, with the mountains protecting the vines and the sea ensuring that the temperature never drops too low during the winter, the results are exceptional wines full of character. The grapes planted include autochthon grapes such as the Montepulciano and the Trebbiano D&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo and more international ones such as the Cabernet Sauvignon or the Chardonnay that have found in the Jasci &amp; Marchesani estate their perfect habitat. Jasci &amp; Marchesani keeps experimenting implanting new grapes and using new wine making technique. 
This double magnum is also the perfect gift idea not only for wine lovers. 


Montepulciano d'Abruzzo is a deeply colored, full-bodied organic red wine.</description>
    <name>Montepulciano d Abruzzo Magnum, Organic Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A rich, powerful, full bodied Sicilian white wine made with &lt;b&gt;Cataratto&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Grillo&lt;/b&gt;, native grapes of Sicily from Donnadicoppe a family run winery, this white wine shows ripe pear and white peach aromas with scents of citrus. Dry and fresh in the mouth</description>
    <name>Cataratto Grillo Nativo, DonnadiCoppe</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An important, elegant and powerful blend of Merlot and Cabernet Sauvignon aged for 6 months in barriques from vineyards located in the west coast of Sicily from Donnadicoppe a family run winery.  A full bodied wine with mature fruit aromas, brambles and blackcurrant, and a round, spicy warmth. The Cabernet balances the fruit with a drier more mineral quality and eight months in oak give the wine structure and intensity.</description>
    <name>Merlot-Cabernet Nativo, DonnadiCoppe</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Nero d&amp;rsquo;Avola is the most planted grape in Sicily where produces fantastic wines like this Nero d&amp;rsquo;Avola, full bodied, powerful with an intense and rich nose of black fruit and an enduring and persistent finish. Donnadicoppe is a family run winery with vineyards in the west coast of Sicily.</description>
    <name>Nero D'Avola, DonnadiCoppe</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This dessert wine made with selected hand picked Grillo grapes, using the passito method, drying the grapes to obtain a concentrated juice, has an intense golden yellow colour and, though sweet, retains its, fresh fruit driven qualities with a delicate balance between honeyed sweetness and fruity acidity</description>
    <name>Grillo Passito Nativo, DonnadiCoppe</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This dessert wine made with selected hand picked Nero d&amp;rsquo;Avola grapes, using the passito method, drying the grapes to obtain a concentrated juice, has an intense ruby red colour, with a nose of mature red fruit, delicately sweet in the mouth, equilibrated and nicely persistent</description>
    <name>Nero d'Avola Passito Nativo, DonnadiCoppe</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A blend made with a native grape, the Nero d&amp;rsquo;Avola, and an international, Syrah, that has found in Sicily a perfect soil to grow and ripe. This full bodied red wine has a powerful, rich, nose of mature red fruit, wild plum, and chocolate. In the mouth, it is well balanced, round and with an enduring aftertaste. </description>
    <name>Syrah-Nero d'Avola Nativo, DonnadiCoppe</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Nebbiolo, the wine is often called young Barolo because made with the same grape than the more famous cousin, is a classy, medium bodied red wine. On the nose it shows aromas of mature fruit with scents of ripe prune. In the mouth, is pleasantly soft. A very well balanced, round and smooth red wine with soft tannins 
</description>
    <name>Nebbiolo d'Alba Lirano, Rivetto</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A full bodied, elegant, red wine made mainly with &lt;b&gt;Cannonau&lt;/b&gt; and a small percentages of &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Merlot&lt;/b&gt; variable depending on the vintage, &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; for 4 months in barrels. This wine shows a complex bouquet with scents of red fruits and underlying hints of vanilla. In the mouth is dry, warm and with a long and lingering aftertaste</description>
    <name>Noriolo, Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Our award winning team has put together a mixed case of organic red and white wines to introduce you to the wonderful and broad world of Italian wines. The selection includes red and white wines from different regions and different style to suit all tastes, all made by passionate producers. The organic mixed case range varies from a full body Chianti Riserva to a Pinot Grigio from Friuli passing from an all time favourite Montepulciano d'Abruzzo. 
The case contains:
2 Ribolla (Friuli)
A white wine with an intense, aromatic but yet, elegant, beautiful floral nose. Medium bodied, dry, refreshing and with a mouth-filling texture and a lasting aftertaste.
2 Riesling (Abruzzo)
A straw yellow colour, with an attractive, complex bouquet with floral and tropical aromas, pleasant, dry and soft in the mouth with an extra bit of weight.
2 Chenti (Friuli)
A full bodied blend of Cabernet Franc and Refosco del Peduncolo rosso producing a ruby red wine with scents of spices and ripe cherry.
2 Pinot Grigio del Collio (Friuli)
A light yellow colour and an intense but delicate nose of flowers and white fruit. 
2 Chianti Riserva 2003 (Tuscany)
A full body red wine with a good structure and a red fruits bouquet. 
2 Montepulciano d'Abruzzo (Abruzzo)
A full bodied, ruby red wine, with a complex bouquet and a long aftertaste. </description>
    <name>Italian organic wines mixed case - SAVE 20%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of Italian organic wines. The case includes 2 bottles each of: Chianti Riserva 2000,
Chianti, 
Racemo Rosso,
Pinot Grigio,
Frascati,
Sauvignon            </description>
    <name>Organic mixed Case (6 reds and 6 whites)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of red wines chosen by our award winning team. The case include: 
3  Chianti Organic
3 Montepulciano d'Abruzzo Organic
3 40/60 Organic
3 Cabernet Franc Organic</description>
    <name>Organic Mixed Red Case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of Italian organic red wines. The case includes 2 bottles each of: Chianti Riserva 2000,
Chianti, 
Racemo Rosso,
Cabernet Franc,
Refosco,
Concento</description>
    <name>Organic mixed red case (12 bottles)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Our award winning team has put together a mixed case of white wines to introduce you to the wonderful world of Italian white wines. The wines chosen come from different regions and are of different style all made by passionate producers. The selection varies from an organic Riesling to a full bodied slightly oaked organic Fiano from Campania. The case includes wines to suit all tastes and for every occasion
The case contains:
2 Riesling (Abruzzo)
2 Pinot Grigio delle Venezie (Veneto)
A refreshing and easy to drink Pinot Grigio with a fresh bouquet of fruits. 
2 Tocai Friulano (Friuli)
2 Chardonnay (Tuscany)
Refreshing with a nose of citrus combined with more mature fruits. 
2 Fiano (Campania) 
2 Vermentino Vigna di Isalle (Sardinia)
A wine with an elegant bouquet and a dry, smooth taste</description>
    <name>Italian mixed white case - SAVE 20%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of Italian organic white wines. The case includes 2 bottles each of: 
Pinot grigio,
Frascati,
Dacis,
Sauvignon,
Chardonnay,
Trebbiano</description>
    <name>Organic mixed white case (12 bottles)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from grapes from vineyard surrounding the town of Orvieto, the classic, historical area, this &lt;b&gt;orvieto classico&lt;/b&gt; is dry and refreshing and has an intense and delicate nose of flowers characteristic of the wine. Fresh on the palate with a full, slightly bittery ending. </description>
    <name>Orvieto Classico, San Marco</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A delicious dessert wine, with an intense gold colour and a rich nose of mature fruit and honey and underlying hints of vanilla. In the mouth is full, warm and with a moderate sweetness. Persistent with a long and clean finish. This dessert wine, made with selected &lt;b&gt;garganega&lt;/b&gt; grapes, is obtained using the passito method leaving the grapes to dry for six months in temperature controlled room and ageing for 12 months in small oak barrels.</description>
    <name>Passito del Casale, Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A &lt;b&gt;pinot bianco&lt;/b&gt; with a bursting floral nose with honey nuances, full, elegant, fruity in the mouth, melon and apricot above all, and a lively acidity for this fantastic white wine made with 100% &lt;b&gt;pinot bianco&lt;/b&gt; grapes, late harvesting, from vineyards in the Colli Orientali area in Friuli</description>
    <name>Pinot Bianco Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A delicate and light &lt;b&gt;spumante&lt;/b&gt;, to be enjoyed with or without food, obtained from Pinot Bianco and Chardonnay grapes using the Charmat method in which the second fermentation takes place in the tank. It is moreish, packed with delicious, soft, floral flavours and a fine perlage that lingers seductively in the mouth.</description>
    <name>Spumante Pinot Chardonnay, Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A &lt;b&gt;Pinot grigio delle Venezie&lt;/b&gt; with a brilliant straw yellow colour with green reflections and a captivating fruity bouquet with scents of pear juice and banana above all. Refreshing and soft with a smooth, dry finish and a lovely fruit acid balance. Obtained from hand picked &lt;b&gt;pinot grigio&lt;/b&gt; grapes.</description>
    <name>Pinot Grigio delle Venezie, Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Pinot Grigio, obtained with 100% &lt;b&gt;pinot grigio&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards located in the DOC area called Lison Pramaggiore, south east of Veneto, has a light golden yellow colour and a distinctive and delicate aroma of orange flowers. It is harmonious and round, with character and elegance.</description>
    <name>Pinot Grigio, La braghina</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A classy, elegant, harmonious &lt;b&gt;pinot noir&lt;/b&gt; produced in Tuscany, in the Chianti area from selected hand picked &lt;b&gt;pinot noir&lt;/b&gt; grapes. &lt;b&gt;Pinot noir&lt;/b&gt; is a grape difficult to grow and a difficult wine to make, but when made properly, it is capable of producing extraordinary, amazing, first class wines. This wine has aromas of black currant, brier rose, red fruits and underlying hints of vanilla. In the mouth, is well balanced, complex and with a lasting aftertaste with well integrated sweet tannins. It is recommended to decant the wine before opening and allow at least one hour.
</description>
    <name>Pinot Noir Patrizia, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The &lt;b&gt;pinot noir&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;nero&lt;/b&gt; is a difficult grape to grow and a difficult wine to make and La Braghina has succeeded where many have failed offering fantastic value for money. Made with 100% &lt;b&gt;pinot noir&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards located in the DOC area called Lison Pramaggiore, south east of Veneto, this &lt;b&gt;pinot noir&lt;/b&gt; has the characteristic nose reminiscent of black pepper and spices, a dry flavour, sweet tannins and a lingering aftertaste</description>
    <name>Pinot noir, La Braghina</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made from a blend of 70% &lt;b&gt;Sangiovese&lt;/b&gt;, 15% &lt;b&gt;Merlot&lt;/b&gt; and 5% &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon&lt;/b&gt; grapes grown in vineyards located around the town of Cortona in Tuscany, between Siena and Arezzo, and aged for 4 months in new and used oak barrels, this Tuscan red wine has a rich and elegant bouquet of mature fruits, with hints of prunes and cherry, and spicy notes with a touch of vanilla. Medium bodied, smooth and round in the mouth with soft tannins.</description>
    <name>Sangiovese Preziosaterra Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An organic blend of &lt;b&gt;Sangiovese&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Cesanese&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; for 6 months in oak barrels. Made with selected grapes from vineyards located in Latium, this wine is elegant, well balanced and velvety on the palate. It has a complex nose showing aromas of red fruit with scents of vanilla. This red wine is suitable for vegan</description>
    <name>Racemo Rosso Organic L'Olivella</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from &lt;b&gt;refosco&lt;/b&gt; grapes organically grown, from vineyards in the area called Colli Orientali del Friuli, this organic red wine has an intense, red ruby colour with very good structure, underwood fruity scents, sometimes a little bit herby. In the mouth, the wine has a good acidity and a persistent fruit. This wine has won a Decanter bronze medal</description>
    <name>Refosco dal Peduncolo Organic Montalbano</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A brilliant, lively, ruby colour red wine with the characteristical spicy nose with an unmissable aroma of violets. In the mouth, is dry and well balanced with light tannins and a lingering aftertaste. Made with hand picked, selected grapes of Prugnolo Gentile which is a clone of the Sangiovese grape, obtained from vineyards around the town of Montepulciano in Tuscany from the Godiolo family.</description>
    <name>Rosso di Montepulciano, Godiolo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A blend of &lt;b&gt;Merlot&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon aged&lt;/b&gt; in small oak barrels. The Rosso Scuro, the name means dark red, is a red wine with an intense ruby colour and a nose that shows aromas of red fruits and spices with underlying hints of vanilla. Full bodied, in the mouth is structured, well balanced, velvety and persistent in the magnum version, perfect for a big party or for a welcome present. This wine has von several international and Italian awards, including the 3 glasses from the Gambero Rosso</description>
    <name>Rosso Scuro Magnum, Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A blend of &lt;b&gt;Merlot&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon aged&lt;/b&gt; in small oak barrels. The Rosso Scuro, the name means dark red, is a red wine with an intense ruby colour and a nose that shows aromas of red fruits and spices with underlying hints of vanilla. Full bodied, in the mouth is structured, well balanced, velvety and persistent. This wine is another masterpiece of Roberto Scubla. This wine has von several international and Italian awards, including the 3 glasses from the Gambero Rosso</description>
    <name>Rosso Scuro Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The &lt;b&gt;montepulciano d'Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt; is a grape that ages well and can produce some fantastic wines. This full bodied red wine, made only with hand picked and selected grapes from a single vineyard, the Rudhir, has been &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; for 18 months in oak barrels and additional 2 years in the bottle, has an intense but delicate nose with scents of cherries and hints of vanilla. Warm, elegant, expressive and very smooth in the mouth with a lasting ending</description>
    <name>Montepulciano d Abruzzo Riserva Organic, Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made from hand picked Sangiovese grapes from vineyards located around the town of Cortona, between Siena and Arezzo, in Tuscany this fantastic wine is fresh, refreshing if drunk at a couple of degree cooler, delightful fragrant and with an inviting fruity nose with scents of cherry and spices. Delicate in the mouth, is balanced, with soft tannins and light to taste. 
</description>
    <name>Sangiovese Selverello Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A masterpiece. Another award winning Italian white wine created by Roberto Scubla. This white wine has a straw yellow colour and an aromatic nose. Round in the mouth, fresh and fruity with a clearly soft and long aftertaste. Only a few thousand bottles produced each year.</description>
    <name>Speziale Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A Supertuscany made with hand picked and selected &lt;b&gt;sangiovese&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;cabernet sauvignon&lt;/b&gt; grapes from, organically grown, old vines from vineyards located near Arezzo &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in small french barrique. An elegant, complex, expressive red wine, rich, with aromas of red fruits, liquorice and cherry with underlying hints of vanilla. Full bodied, soft and velvety in the mouth</description>
    <name>Stroncoli, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Produced from grapes obtained from vineyards located between Siena and Arezzo grown organically, in San Savino, this red wine is made only using the best grapes of Sangiovese and Cabernet Sauvignon. Belonging to the Supertuscany&amp;rsquo;s category, this red wine has an intense red ruby color with a slight tendency to garnet, and a rich nose of red fruits, liquorice, cherry and vanilla aroma. Rich and complex, with a good body and tannic concentration, soft and velvety, very persistent. This wine in its magnum version is also an ideal present for an Italian wine lover.</description>
    <name>Stroncoli Magnum, Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The hamper contains:
&amp;#149;	Balsamic vinegar aged 2 years
&amp;#149;	Easy to cook pasta or rice
&amp;#149;	Organic specialty in extra virgin olive oil
&amp;#149;	2 pasta sauces
&amp;#149;	2 specialties in extra virgin olive oil
&amp;#149;  2 olives in extra virgin olive oil
&amp;#149;	2 pates in extra virgin olive oil
&amp;#149;	Organic Extra virgin olive oil in amphora
&amp;#149;	2 bottles of red wine
&amp;#149;	2 bottles of white wine
&amp;#149;	1 box of pasta

</description>
    <name>Summer Special Edition</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Running out of ideas? Looking for something that will make an impression? Our luxury hamper is the perfect answer. Offering a selection of the best Italian wine and food available, it is the gift everyone wants to receive. The Luxury hamper is a basket full of mouth watering produces. Starting with the Pinot Grigio as an aperitif and conclude sipping our artisan made cantuccini in the espresso. 
A basket full of mouth watering Italian food and wine to send to friends, relatives, employees and customers all year round, the perfect gift idea, especially a Christmas. All our hampers come wrapped and with a personalised card.

The hamper contains: 
1 box of artisan made cantuccini al cioccolato 200gr
1 Modena balsamic vinegar aged 5 years
1 asparagus in extra virgin olive oil
1 bottle of Umbrian extra virgin olive oil Viola 750cl 
1 pate of green olives in extra virgin olive oil
1 bottle of Chianti Classico
1 bottle of Pinot Grigio Dal Cero
1 artichokes in extra virgin olive oil 280gr
1 mixed mushroom in extra virgin olive oil
1 aubergines in extra virgin olive oil   

For more information about our Corporate hampers, please give us a call on 0191 565 4884. 
</description>
    <name>Luxury hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An introduction to Italian wines selected by our wines experts. 
The case contains two bottles each of the following wines:

Sparkling: Castel del Picco Prosecco
White 2006 : Dal Cero Pinot Grigio IGT delle Venezie
White 2006 :Donnardea Colli Albani Superiore
Rose' 2005: Jasci &amp; Marchesani Cerasuolo d'Abruzzo
Red 2005: Jasci &amp; Marchesani Montepulciano d'Abruzzo Organic
Red 2004: Dal Cero Selverello (Sangiovese from Tuscany.
</description>
    <name>Taste of Italy</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A special mixed case containing a selection of wines that will please everyone, from the elegant organic Refosco  to a rich falanghina, and the award winning wine Preziosaterra. The cases contains 2 bottles each of the following wines:

&lt;b&gt;Refosco del peduncolo rosso&lt;/b&gt; (Organic, Decanter Bronze winner)
An organic red wine with an intense, red ruby colour with very good structure, underwood fruity scents, sometimes a little bit herby. In the mouth, the wine has a good acidity and a persistent fruit. 

&lt;b&gt;Trebbiano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt; (organic)
A full bodied organic Trebbiano d'Abruzzo with a gold colour, a full and intense nose with aromas of white fruit and a long ending. Refreshing and lively with a lovely acid balance

&lt;b&gt;Vermentino&lt;/b&gt;
A vermentino with a light gold colour, with character, light, with an intense, fruity nose with notes of citrus and almonds and a delicate, persistent bouquet. Full-bodied, with medium acidity.

&lt;b&gt;Falanghina&lt;/b&gt;
A white wine with tempting aromas of apples and pears with underlying notes of almonds. Obtained from 100% falanghina grapes from very old vines, this wine is full bodied but crispy and with a nice texture, fresh and with a mineral finish.

&lt;b&gt;Preziosaterra&lt;/b&gt; (IWC and Decanter bronze medal winner)
A blend of Sangiovese, Merlot and Cabernet sauvignon grapes aged for 4 months in new and used oak barrels, this Tuscan red wine has a rich and elegant bouquet of mature fruits, with hints of prunes and cherry, and spicy notes with a touch of vanilla. Medium bodied, soft and round in the mouth.

&lt;b&gt;Selverello&lt;/b&gt;
Made from hand picked Sangiovese grapes this fantastic value wine is fresh, refreshing if drunk at a couple of degree cooler, delightful fragrant with an inviting fruity nose with scents of cherry and spices. Delicate 
in the mouth, balanced and light to taste.

&lt;font size= "-2"&gt;We reserve the right to substitute any of the wine with a similar or more expensive wine&lt;/font&gt;</description>
    <name>Taste of Italy mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Intense ruby red colour with light garnet hues. Complex with aromas of tobacco, blackberry and blackcurrant jam and a light hint of sweet, nicely rounded tannins in the finish and a silky palate make the 2003 vintage a very elegant version of this award winning wines</description>
    <name>Tignanello, Antinori</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from 100% &lt;b&gt;tocai friulano&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards located in the Colli Orientali area in Friuli, this wine has a smooth, fine and delicate floral nose with the typical almond flavour, more or less noticeable depending on the vintage, and round in the mouth with a lasting ending</description>
    <name>Tocai Friulano Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A full bodied organic &lt;b&gt;Trebbiano d'Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt; with a gold colour, a full and intense nose with aromas of white fruit and a long ending. Refreshing and lively with a lovely acid balance</description>
    <name>Trebbiano d Abruzzo Organic Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fragrant, light red wine easy to enjoy with or without food. Made from &lt;b&gt;Corvina&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Rondinella&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Molinara&lt;/b&gt;, this &lt;b&gt;Valpolicella&lt;/b&gt; has a lively bouquet, with floral aromas and hints of cherry or berry fruits. On the palate is light, fruity, and with a pleasant touch of acidity that leaves a clean finish. It is a perfect example of a traditional Valpolicella wine</description>
    <name>Valpolicella Valetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Rich, elegant &lt;b&gt;verduzzo friulano&lt;/b&gt;, with an intense amber colour and a nose of acacia honey, nut and hints of vanilla. In the mouth is pleasantly sweet, concentrated, velvety, soft, supported by the typical tannin of the grape. This wine has won several Italian and international awards, including the 3 glasses from the Gambero Rosso. A masterpiece. Another award winning Italian dessert wine created by Roberto Scubla. The grapes of &lt;b&gt;verduzzo friulano&lt;/b&gt;, dried on the trellis and exposed to the Bora winds are then fermented in barriques. This method is called &amp;ldquo;passimento&amp;rdquo; thus the name for dessert wines that follows that method of &amp;ldquo;passito&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    <name>Verduzzo Friulano Passito "Cratis" Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another award winning Italian white wine from Roberto Scubla. Obtained from Verduzzo grapes, native grape of Friuli, from vineyards in the Colli Orientali area, the grapes are harvested late and dried on the vine to give a more intense flavour. The result is a wine with a deep golden yellow colour with acacia and honey hints, a balanced tannin and is pleasantly medium sweet.</description>
    <name>Verduzzo Friulano Scubla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A &lt;b&gt;vermentino&lt;/b&gt; with a light gold colour, with character, light, with an intense, fruity nose with notes of citrus and almonds and a delicate, persistent bouquet. Full-bodied, with medium acidity. </description>
    <name>Vermentino Isalle Bianco, Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This &lt;b&gt;Vin Santo Riserva&lt;/b&gt; is made only with the best grapes, left over riping on the vines and then dried for three months in boxes before they are turned into wine and aged in barriques for more than 10 years. The result is a dessert wine with a golden colour, rich, generous and with a nose with aromas of honey, walnuts and dried fruit amongst others. Well structured, smooth and velvety, pleasantly sweet and with a long ending. The &lt;b&gt;Vin Santo&lt;/b&gt; is probably the most known Italian dessert wines and La Casaccia's is a superb example. </description>
    <name>Vin Santo Riserva 1997, La Casaccia</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Vino Nobile di Montepulciano made from only the best Canaiolo e Prugnolo gentile grapes, Sangiovese clones, is a big red for quality, body, structure. Made with grapes grown on the hills of Montepulciano, Tuscany, this Tuscan red is an elegant wine with a grainy red colour and a delicate, but intense, aromas of chocolate, leather' spice, eucalyptus and vanilla. Rich, smooth and full with a lasting finish. It is recommended to decant the wine before opening. 

"One rarely comes across a Vino Nobile di Montepulciano this authentic at a price this reasonable. A small-production, artisanal wine, it falls into the get-it-while-you-can category." Matt Kramer, Oregonlive.com
</description>
    <name>Vino Nobile di Montepulciano 2004, Godiolo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This high quality organic traditional &lt;b&gt;Modena balsamic vinegar&lt;/b&gt; has been made with organically grown grapes. It is smooth and rich with a slight sweetness. Excellent on salads, pasta, pizza, bread and to flavor sauces. Also used on ice cream, dessert and to make cocktails</description>
    <name>Modena Balsamic vinegar organic</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>&lt;b&gt;Cesanese&lt;/b&gt; is a native grape from Latium that has previously been used to make blends and it is now vinified on its own. This &lt;b&gt;Cesanese&lt;/b&gt; is made using the ripasso method, which consist in "repassing" the juice on the skinks, same method used for the Ripasso della Valpolicella. The wine is then &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; for 12 months in oak barrels to add spicy, creamy hints. This wine shows aromas of berries and red fruit with an underlying hints of vanilla. On the mouth, is elegant, rich and smooth. This red wine is suitable for vegans</description>
    <name>Cesanese, Organic L'Olivella</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fresh and fragrant light medium sweet wine. This &lt;b&gt;orvieto abboccato&lt;/b&gt;, is made from grapes grown in vineyards located in the classic, historical area. This medium sweet white wine shows a floral nose. It is harmonious and delicious in the mouth, a good body with a hint of sweetness and an aftertaste of citrus fruits</description>
    <name>Orvieto Abboccato, San Marco</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Rosso di Montalcino is an exceptional pure expression of Sangiovese unoaked. It shows floral aromas with scents of plum, cherry along with a full palate and a nice lingering finish. Obtained from Sangiovese grapes from vineyards located in the Montalcino area. </description>
    <name>Rosso di Montalcino, La Gerla</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fresh, inviting Moscato d&amp;rsquo;Asti, a white wine slightly sparkling for a rich cheese cake or going solo as an afternoon aperitif. This Moscato d&amp;rsquo;Asti has a delicate nose bursting with scents of ripe peaches and candied. It has a low alcohol content and a sweet end. Made with 100% Muscat grapes from vineyards located around the town of Asti, in Piedmont from the Rivetto family. </description>
    <name>Moscato d'Asti, Rivetto</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Outstanding, complex, rich, full, silky. This &lt;b&gt;Chianti Classico Riserva&lt;/b&gt; is all of the above and much more. Made using only the best Sangiovese grapes and aged in small barrels, barriques, it has a ruby color tending to garnet with ageing, is complex on the nose with, initially, hints of vanilla that then become berries, tobacco, smoke, and many more aromas. In the mouth is well balanced, round, elegant, silky and harmonious. The finish is long and with a fine and delicate aftertaste. To fully appreciate the wine, it is recommended to decant it</description>
    <name>Chianti Classico Riserva 2003, La Casaccia</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The bottle not only contains 3 liters of a clean, fresh and elegant Prosecco, with delicate, persistent bubbles that enhance its subtle citrusy fruit but it also the perfect idea for a present, the perfect celebration tool. </description>
    <name>Prosecco Double Magnum, Bellenda</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Exceptional Italian DOP extra virgin olive oil. Cold pressed. A light, delicate oil ideal for fish and vegetables. A dark bottle protect the oil from the damages of the light.</description>
    <name>Italian DOP extra virgin olive oil from Liguria 500ml, Aziende di Burana</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This extra virgin olive oil is obtained from a single estate in &lt;b&gt;Tuscany&lt;/b&gt;, cold pressed olives. The olives are hand picked and immediately pressed through a mechanical press. The result is a oil with a very low acidity and of green colour offering hints of hay and olives. This oil is produced in very small quantity</description>
    <name>Extra Virgin Olive Oil, Dal Cero </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic &lt;b&gt;Chianti Classico&lt;/b&gt;, or Gallo Nero as often it is called, with a complex nose with notes of cherries and spices above all.  Made only with the best Sangiovese grapes and aged in big barrels, it is soft and round with smooth tannins. Good texture and balance complete this Chianti Classico. The finish is persistent and mouth filling. A classic of Italian wines </description>
    <name>Chianti Classico 2005 , La Casaccia</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made only with hand picked Garganega grapes from vineyards surrounding the town of Soave, near Verona, the Soave is one of the most famous Italian wines and Dal Cero is one of the coming producers. The Soave has become a bland, tasteless, cheap wine, however, when made properly it could be a fantastic wine. This is one of the best, with a rich nose with aromas of white fruits. In the mouth is refreshing, vibrant, textured and with the characteristic final hints of almonds 
</description>
    <name>Soave Corte Giacobbe, Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This dessert wine is obtained from selected organically grown grapes of Malvasia puntinata, Malvasia rossa, Bellone, native grapes from Latium, using the passito method and aged in small oak barrels. This passito shows floral aromas with scents of vanilla on the nose, in the mouth is soft, fresh and with a lingering aftertaste. This wine is suitable for vegan</description>
    <name>Passito Organic Tre Grome, L'Olivella</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A full bodied &lt;b&gt;Chardonnay riserva&lt;/b&gt;from grapes organically grown in Abruzzo, near the sea, and aged for 18 months in barrique to add creamy hints to a rich nose that shows aromas of peach and apricot. In the mouth, is full, soft and velvety with an elegant finish. </description>
    <name>Chardonnay Organic Riserva, Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These Italian artichokes, roasted and preserved in olive oil with a very delicate taste are ideal as a side dish or an ingredient. The artichokes are put in olive oil immediately after being roasted to preserve their full flavour. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Roasted artichokes, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Italian red peppers stuffed with tuna, cappers and mushrooms preserved in extra virgin olive oil, ideal on its own as an aperitif or a side plate. Made using only the freshest ingredients without any preservative, this Italian specialty will surprise you</description>
    <name>Pepper with Tuna in Extra Virgin Olive Oil, Triveri </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This made is made following the original recipe. It can be used on pasta, the genoan tradition says strozzapreti o trenette, but it is now widely used in the Italian cuisine. For recipes, visit our recipe section. </description>
    <name>Organic Pesto</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this olive oil  is an extra virgin olive oil of green color with a golden, medium fruity flavour and slightly pungent on the finish.</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil Tradizionale, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of green color with a golden, medium to intense fruity flavour and an harmonious balance of bitterness and pungency. </description>
    <name>DOP Italian extra virgin olive oil Colleruita Viola 100ml</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of green color with a golden, medium to intense fruity flavour and an harmonious balance of bitterness and pungency. The oil comes in a in a beautifully shaped bottle with dispenser</description>
    <name>DOP Italian extra virgin olive oil Colleruita 250ml, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of green color with a golden, medium to intense fruity flavour and an harmonious balance of bitterness and pungency. The oil comes in a in a beautifully shaped bottle with dispenser</description>
    <name>DOP Italian extra virgin olive oil Colleruita 500ml, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of green color and with a rich fruity olive taste typical of the Moraiolo olive variety.</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil Il Sincero 100ml, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of green color and with a rich fruity olive taste typical of the Moraiolo olive variety.  The oil comes in a beautifully shaped bottle with dispenser</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil Il Sincero 250ml, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of green color and with a rich fruity olive taste typical of the Moraiolo olive variety.  The oil comes in a beautifully shaped bottle with dispenser</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil Il Sincero 500ml, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of  green color with golden tinges, slightly bitter and pungent. </description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil Inprivio 100ml, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of  green color with golden tinges, slightly bitter and pungent. The oil comes in a in a beautifully shaped bottle with dispenser</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil Inprivio 250ml, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this extra virgin olive oil is an olive oil of  green color with golden tinges, slightly bitter and pungent. The oil comes in a in a beautifully shaped bottle with dispenser</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil Inprivio 500ml, Viola</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These are the biscuits for the sweet toothed and at Italyabroad we are......A crunchy, handmade Cantuccini biscuits with whole almonds and plenty of chocolate bits in between, a  reinterpretation of the classic Tuscan biscuit. These cantuccini can be eaten on their own or offered with coffees or teas.  Made only with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients, they are addictive, if you start, you can&amp;rsquo;t stop until they are finished. </description>
    <name>Cantuccini with Chocolate</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>What a cantuccini&amp;#133; Another fantastic combination for these cantuccini with bits of dark chocolate and dried oranges. The taste is great, the freshness of the orange with the bitterness of the cocoa works very well. These cantuccini are made with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients. </description>
    <name>Cantuccini Cocoa and Oranges</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another excited combination. Handmade cantuccini with pistachio Cantuccini with pistachio and cocoa where the saltiness of the pistachio blend perfectly into the cocoa creating a unique flavour in a nice box. These cantuccini are made with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients. </description>
    <name>Cantuccini Cocoa and Pistachio </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>What a cantuccini&amp;#133; the bitter taste of the almond combined with the freshness and of the candied lemon and the sweetness of the biscuit. One of our preferred&amp;#133; Made in Tuscany, using only natural and high quality ingredients, from Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato that has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique biscuits and cakes. BUY 1 GET 1 FREE</description>
    <name>Cantuccini with candied lemon, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Crunchy cantuccini with apricot, where the result is a discerning and elegant biscuit in a nice box. These cantuccini are made with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients. </description>
    <name>Cantuccini with Apricots</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A tasteful and rich biscuit made from Antica Pasticceria Betti with nuts, almonds, dried fruits, honey and anise. Made in Tuscany, using only natural and high quality ingredients, from Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato that has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique biscuits and cakes. BUY 1 GET 1 FREE</description>
    <name>Cavallucci, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From Tuscany, the famous Italian region, Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique cantuccini. Antica Pasticceria Betti has been recognized for their creative combination using only all-natural and high quality ingredients. You surely will love the light flavour of their biscuits or cakes. There is no doubt that Antica Pasticceria Betti will quickly become your favourite bakers to give as a gift or share with others and experience the old way of baking.  The traditional Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruits, nut, and honey cake. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.</description>
    <name>Traditional Panforte 500gr, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The traditional Panforte, a Tuscan Christmas cake, is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruits, nut, and honey cake. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar. BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</description>
    <name>Handmade traditional panforte, Antica Pasticceria Betti  BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From Tuscany, the famous Italian region, Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique cantuccini. Antica Pasticceria Betti has been recognized for their creative combination using only all-natural and high quality ingredients. You surely will love the light flavour of their biscuits or cakes. There is no doubt that Antica Pasticceria Betti will quickly become your favourite bakers to give as a gift or share with others and experience the old way of baking. This Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruits, nut, and honey cake with a touch of cinnamon. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.
</description>
    <name>Panforte Pan Pepato 500gr, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From Tuscany, the famous Italian region, Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique cantuccini. Antica Pasticceria Betti has been recognized for their creative combination using only all-natural and high quality ingredients. You surely will love the light flavour of their biscuits or cakes. There is no doubt that Antica Pasticceria Betti will quickly become your favourite bakers to give as a gift or share with others and experience the old way of baking. This Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruits, nut, and honey cake with a touch of cinnamon. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.</description>
    <name>Panforte Pan Pepato 300gr, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From Tuscany, the famous Italian region, Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique cantuccini. Antica Pasticceria Betti has been recognized for their creative combination using only all-natural and high quality ingredients. You surely will love the light flavour of their biscuits or cakes. There is no doubt that Antica Pasticceria Betti will quickly become your favourite bakers to give as a gift or share with others and experience the old way of baking. This Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruit, nut, and honey cake with plenty of almonds. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.
</description>
    <name>Panforte Margherita 500gr, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruit, nut, and honey cake with plenty of almonds. This panforte, like all other Tuscan specialties baked by the Antica Pasticceria Betti, is handmade and uses the finest almonds, dried apricots, nectarines, peaches, and dates with no artificial additives. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.
</description>
    <name>Panforte Margherita 300gr,  Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From Tuscany, the famous Italian region, Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique cantuccini. Antica Pasticceria Betti has been recognized for their creative combination using only all-natural and high quality ingredients. You surely will love the light flavour of their biscuits or cakes. There is no doubt that Antica Pasticceria Betti will quickly become your favourite bakers to give as a gift or share with others and experience the old way of baking. This Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruit, nut, and honey cake wetted with the finest Chianti. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.
</description>
    <name>Panforte al Chianti 500gr, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This handmade traditional Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruit, nut, and honey cake wetted with the unique taste of Vin Santo in a Christmas themed box . Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar. BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</description>
    <name>Handmade panforte al Vin Santo, Antica Pasticceria Betti BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From Tuscany, the famous Italian region, Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique cantuccini. Antica Pasticceria Betti has been recognized for their creative combination using only all-natural and high quality ingredients. You surely will love the light flavour of their biscuits or cakes. There is no doubt that Antica Pasticceria Betti will quickly become your favourite bakers to give as a gift or share with others and experience the old way of baking. This traditional Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruit, nut, and honey cake wetted with the unique taste of Vin Santo. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.
</description>
    <name>Panforte al Vin Santo 500gr,  Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This handmade Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruit, nut, and honey cake wetted with the finest Chianti in a Christmas themed box. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar. BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE
</description>
    <name>Handmade panforte al Chianti, Antica Pasticceria Betti  BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From Tuscany, the famous Italian region, Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique cantuccini. Antica Pasticceria Betti has been recognized for their creative combination using only all-natural and high quality ingredients. You surely will love the light flavour of their biscuits or cakes. There is no doubt that Antica Pasticceria Betti will quickly become your favourite bakers to give as a gift or share with others and experience the old way of baking. This traditional Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruit, nut, and honey cake wetted with the unique taste of the Moscato wine from Piedmont. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.</description>
    <name>Panforte al Vino Moscato 500gr, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From Tuscany, the famous Italian region, Antica Pasticceria Betti in Prato has been baking fine Italian biscuits and cakes since 1940 and has created a line of flavourful and unique cantuccini. Antica Pasticceria Betti has been recognized for their creative combination using only all-natural and high quality ingredients. You surely will love the light flavour of their biscuits or cakes. There is no doubt that Antica Pasticceria Betti will quickly become your favourite bakers to give as a gift or share with others and experience the old way of baking. This traditional Panforte is a wonderfully chewy and delicious fruit, nut, and honey cake wetted with the unique taste of the Moscato wine from Piedmont. Enjoy it thinly sliced at the end of the meal or as a long-lasting, nutritious energy bar.</description>
    <name>Panforte al Vino Moscato 300gr, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Pandoro is the other Italian classic Christmas cake. There cannot be be Christmas without eating pandoro o panettone and drinking spumante. However, this is not the classic version of the pandoro, the chef has added candied fruits to give it an additional flavour. This pandoro has been made using only natural ingredients, without preservatives or additives and hand wrapped. To enjoy the pandoro at its best, heat the slice in the oven for a few minutes and let the fragrances invade the kitchen</description>
    <name>Handmade Pandoro, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This is a modern version of a classic cake, this panettone has an additional twist.. the chef added dried figs and almonds to the original recipe. This Panettone has been made using only natural ingredients, without preservatives or additives and hand wrapped. Experience the real taste of the panettone with Antica Pasticceria Betti. To enjoy the panettone at its best, heat the slice in the oven for a few minutes and let the fragrances invade the kitchen 
</description>
    <name>Handmade panettone campagnolo, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another modern version of the classic cake, a panettone has an additional twist.. fruits of the forest. This Panettone  has been made using only natural ingredients, without preservatives or additives and hand wrapped. Experience the real taste of the panettone with Antica Pasticceria Betti. To enjoy the panettone at its best, heat the slice in the oven for a few minutes and let the fragrances invade the kitchen</description>
    <name>Handmade panettone delicato, Antica Pasticceria Betti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This high quality traditional &lt;b&gt;Modena balsamic vinegar&lt;/b&gt; has been aged for at least 5 years in traditional barrels. It is thick, smooth and rich with a slight sweetness. Excellent on salads, pasta, pizza, bread and to flavor sauces. Also used on ice cream, dessert and to make cocktails.</description>
    <name>Modena Balsamic Vinegar aged 5 years</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Exceptional Italian extra virgin olive oil, cold pressed. A light, delicate oil ideal for fish and vegetables. A dark bottle protect the oil from the damages of the light.</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil from Liguria 500ml, Aziende di Burana</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Exceptional Italian extra virgin olive oil, cold pressed. A light, delicate oil ideal for fish and vegetables. A dark bottle protect the oil from the damages of the light.</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil from Liguria 750ml, Aziende di Burana</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Our award winning team has put together a mixed case of light bodied  Italian red and white wines to introduce you to the wonderful and broad world of Italian red wines. The wines chosen come from different regions and are ideal with light meals or snacks. 
The case contains:
2 Refosco del Peduncolo(Friuli, organic)
2 Cabernet Franc(Friuli, organic)
A light Italian red wine with a lively bouquet, with floral notes and hints of cherry fruits 
2 Pinot grigio (Veneto)
A refreshing and easy to drink Pinot Grigio delle Venezie with a fresh bouquet of fruits
2 Selverello (Tuscany)
An Italian red wine made with Sangiovese grapes from Tuscany. A delicate, balanced and light wine to drink. 
2 Bardolino (Veneto)
Light bodied wine, with a fruity nose, particularly strawberries and red cherries hints
2 Chardonnay (Tuscany)
A refreshing Italian white wine, this Chardonnay has a nose of citrus combined with more mature fruits</description>
    <name>Light bites Italian mixed case - SAVE 15%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Our award winning team has put together a mixed case of Italian red and white wines to introduce you to the wonderful and broad world of Italian red wines. The wines chosen come from different regions and are ideal to accompany lunch and dinner. They come delivered to your address free of charge, UK mainland only.
The case contains:
2 Falanghina (Campania, organic)
2 Refosco del peduncolo rosso (Veneto)
An Italian red wine typical of the north east of Italy, has a red ruby colour with very good structure and red fruits scents
2 Filieri Rosato (Sardinia)
Obtained from the Cannonau grapes, this wine is dry, with an intense and persistent bouquet and the same characteristics in the mouth
2 Preziosaterra (Tuscany)
An Italian red wine made with a base Sangiovese grapes from Tuscany slightly oaked and a nose of mature fruits and a spicy note
2 Riesling(Abruzzo, organic)
A rich-looking golden hue Italian white wine with white fruit aromas on the nose to continue this impression in the mouth
2 Chenti (Friuli)
A full bodied Italian red wine made with a blend of Cabernet Franc and Refosco del Peduncolo rosso producing a ruby red wine with scents of spices and ripe cherry</description>
    <name>Lunch and dinner mixed case - SAVE 15%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>White truffle flavoured extra virgin olive oil for your salads</description>
    <name>White truffle flavoured extra virgin olive oil, 250ml</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These whole porcini mushrooms are put immediately in olive oil after being picked to preserve their full flavours. The Porcini mushroom is a rich, meaty mushroom very versatile, delicate or vigorous enough depending of the occasion. For ideas, visit our recipes section. </description>
    <name>Porcini mushrooms, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>In Italy every Christmas, every family, sits together around a big long table and celebrate the arrival of Christmas opening a bottle of Spumante and eating the panettone. This is the Italian Christmas. 

&lt;B&gt;Handmade panettone tradizionale, Antica Pasticceria Betti (750gr)&lt;/B&gt;
This Panettone with dried grapes, has been made using only natural ingredients, without preservatives or additives and hand wrapped. Experience the real taste of the panettone with Antica Pasticceria Betti. 

&lt;B&gt;Spumante Pinot Chardonnay, Dal Cero&lt;/B&gt;
A moreish spumante packed with delicious, soft, floral flavours and a fine perlage that lingers seductively in the mouth</description>
    <name>Handmade traditional Panettone &amp; Spumante - SAVE 10%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Chianti and Panforte are very important parts of the Tuscan tradition. We want to give you the opportunity to experience the Tuscan life sitting comfortably on your kitchen. Our Chianti is a 2004 vintage from Marengo and the Panforte is artisan made from a small bakery, Pasticceria, in Prato.

For more information about our Corporate hampers, please give us a call on 0191 565 4884. </description>
    <name>Chianti &amp; artisan made traditional Panforte 500gr</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>It is probably the most famous Tuscan tradition, sipping the Cantuccini in the Vin Santo. Our handmade traditional cantuccini, made by a small Tuscan bakery, Pasticceria, and our Vin Santo riserva, vintage 1997, of a golden color and honey nose are made for each other and represent a perfect Christmas gift
</description>
    <name>Vin Santo &amp; handmade Cantuccini</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This &lt;b&gt;barolo&lt;/b&gt;, one of the great Italian reds, is the perfect emblem of a fantastic vintage, the 2000. Extremely clean and fresh, with tar and berry aromas, a full bodied palate with fine tannins and an elegant finish. This &lt;b&gt;barolo Rivetto&lt;/b&gt; has won several national and international awards and it has received 4 stars from Decanter in a &lt;b&gt;barolo&lt;/b&gt; tasting
</description>
    <name>Barolo Rivetto 2000, Giulin </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The hamper contains

2 x Pesto 
Trebbiano d'Abruzzo
Pinot grigio 
Chenti 
2 x pasta 
Modena Balsamic vineger 
Extra virgin olive oil
Pasta sauce
</description>
    <name>Organic hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The hamper contains: 

Pinot grigio
Presiozaterra
Selverello
Black olives in extra virgin olive oil
2 x Pasta sauce
Artichokes in extra virgin olive oil
</description>
    <name>Taste of Italy hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A full bodied, red wine obtained mainly from Cannonau grapes from vineyards in one of the most prolific area of Sardinia. This elegant wine shows intense aromas of red fruit. In the mouth is clean, smooth and round with a long ending.</description>
    <name>Cannonau Tunila Rosso IGT, Cantina di Dorgali</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Italyabroad.com wine appreciation group is holding its monthly wine tasting the 23rd of January. The time and venue in Newcastle will be confirmed closer to the date. During the evening, a 3 courses dinner and 5 different wines with our popular "guess the wine" game with plenty of wine to be won, each wine will be introduced by a presentation about the wine and the producer&amp;rsquo;s philosophy. The tasting is very informal and this is the feedback received by one of the attendees at the last tasting: "One of the most enjoyable evenings we've had for a while. Thank you" (J.A. and S.R.)
For more information email us or call the 0191 5654884 Member of the wine club will receive a 25% discount on the ticket.


Andrea</description>
    <name>Wine appreciation club - January tasting</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This organic Cabernet Sauvignon, made with organic grapes grown in Abruzzo, in vineyards located along the cost, is a round and well balanced red wine, with aromas of fruits and spices. In the mouth is full, warm, fruity with soft tannins and a long ending. This wine has been aged in barrels for a few months to add complexity to the it 
</description>
    <name>Cabernet Sauvignon, Organic Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>&lt;br&gt;The ideal Italian wine club. This option is tailor made to give you the maximum benefit with the minimum effort. You will receive a 12 bottle case of wine every three months and you can cancel the membership at any time. You will get to taste and know plenty of Italian wines made by small producers, you will appreciate the differences amongst Italian wines. We think that one of the benefits of being member of a wine club is opening up your mind, sending you wines that you would have never chosen otherwise, however, you are in complete control and you can choose between reds, whites or mixed case if you want to. Each case will help you in broaden your Italian wine horizons, with exclusive hand-picked recommendations and delivered completely FREE of charge. After your special introductory offer, all subsequent cases cost &amp;pound;89.90 with &lt;b&gt;guaranteed savings of at least 30% on every case&lt;/b&gt;. Joining the wine club will also entitle to a 25% discount on our wine tastings and 10% discount on your purchases from Italyabroad.com.</description>
    <name>Wine Club Regular Case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another fantastic vintage for this &lt;b&gt;Chianti Riserva&lt;/b&gt; and Giacomo Marengo. An elegant, classy, full bodied and balanced &lt;b&gt;Chianti Riserva&lt;/b&gt; with aromas of black cherry with hints of vanilla. On the mouth, it has a wonderful structure and great tannic tenderness. Produced in limited quantity. Produced from grapes obtained from vineyards located between Siena and Arezzo, in San Savino, this &lt;b&gt;Chianti Riserva&lt;/b&gt; is made only using the best grapes of &lt;b&gt;Sangiovese&lt;/b&gt; with a small proportion of &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in small french barriques</description>
    <name>Chianti Riserva DOCG 2000 La Commenda, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The wine tasting event, held at La Toscana restaurant in 22 Leazes Park Road Newcastle, will consist of a tasting of 10 different Italian wines with matching buffet that will take you on a journey through the Italian wine making traditions and regions with the Italian wine specialist. 

The wines that will be tasted are:
Lazio Rosso (Latium)
Colli Albani (Latium)
Soave (Veneto)
Pinot grigio (Veneto)
Trebbiano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo (organic, Abruzzo)
Montepulciano D&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo (organic, Abruzzo)
Selverello (sangiovese, Tuscany)
Chianti Riserva 2000 (Tuscany)
Moscato D&amp;rsquo;Asti (Piedmont)
Cratis, Passito friulano (Friuli)

The evening will start at 6.30 and the cost is &amp;pound;10 per person. Reservation is necessary. To reserve your place call La Toscana on 0191 232 5871 or buy the ticket.  

</description>
    <name>Discover Italian wines. A journey through the Italian's wine making tradition</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This journey will take you through the different Italian wines and wine making traditions with the Italian wine specialist, italyabroad.com. The course is divided into 6 different sessions: 
Piedmont (from the Moscato d'Asti to the Barolo)
North (from the Amarone to the superwhites of Friuli)
Tuscany (from the Chianti to the Brunello)
Centre (from the Frascati to the Sagrantino)
South (from the Aglianico to the Primitivo)
Islands (from the Nero d'avola to the Cannonau)

In each session will be tasted a total of 8 different wines, accompanied by tapas, with references to the grapes, soil, climate and producers. If you book the whole course, there is a discount of &amp;pound;30. This session will examine the caractheristics of the wine from Piedmont, from the famous Barolo to the less Grignolino d'Asti. If you would like to know more about the course, please call us on 0191 5654884 or write us a mail. 
</description>
    <name>Discover Italian wines. A journey through the Italian's wine making tradition. Wines from Piedmont</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Vino Nobile di Montepulciano Riserva made from only the best Canaiolo e Prugnolo gentile grapes is a big red for quality, body, structure and particularly price. An elegant wine with a grainy red colour and a delicate, but intense aromas of chocolate, leather' spice, eucalyptus and vanilla. Rich, smooth and full with a lasting finish. The 2001 has been a fantastic vintage for the Montepulciano area and a very limited quantity has been aged longer to produce this fantastic Vino Nobile di Montepulciano Riserva. </description>
    <name>Vino Nobile di Montepulciano 2001 Riserva, Godiolo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Handmade cantuccini where the delicate taste of the figs create another unique, crunchy biscuit with an unique flavour in a nice box ideal as a gift. These cantuccini are made with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients. </description>
    <name>Cantuccini with Figs</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Very unusual but very tasty these handmade cantuccini, the traditional Tuscan biscuit, where the coffee flavour is combined with the bitterly taste of the hazelnts in a nice box. These cantuccini are made with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients. </description>
    <name>Cantuccini with Coffee and Hazelnut</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These mixed Italian mushrooms, freshly-picked, in olive oil are ideal as a side dish or to be used as an ingredient for a main course. The mushrooms are immediately put in olive oil to preserve their full flavour. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Boscaiola mixed mushrooms, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These lampascioni, Italian small onions, are marinated in olive oil and are ideal, with their characteristic taste and freshness, as a side dish to complement meat dishes.</description>
    <name>Lampascioni (wild onions), Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These Italian green olives, marinated, in olive oil are ideal to accompany a glass of prosecco or white wine or to be used as an ingredient for main courses. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Green olives marinate, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These sun dried Italian tomatoes, obtained leaving the tomatoes drying under the Adriatic sun, have a rich and delicious flavour perfect in antipasti or in the preparation of sauces. The sun dried tomatoes are immediately put in olive oil to preserve their full flavour. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Sun dried tomatoes, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The sun dried Italian tomatoes, obtained leaving the tomatoes drying under the Adriatic sun, are then minced and preserved in the olive oil. This pate is perfect for Bruschettas or as ingredient in the preparation of sauces or main courses. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Sun dried tomatoes pate, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A mixed case of Tuscan red wines from the classic Chianti Classico and Chianti to a Sangiovese from the Cortona area with a free bags of artisan made Cantuccini. The Tuscan wines chosen are very different, from a light sangiovese to a full body supertuscany, blend of sangiovese and cabernet sauvignon, including a light and very fruity chardonnay from the Cortona area.
The case contains:
2 Stroncoli
2 Chianti Classico
2 Chianti dei colli aretini Le Tornaie
2 Selverello
2 Preziosaterra
2 Chardonnay
1 bag of artisan made Cantuccini
</description>
    <name>Wines of Tuscany, mixed case of Tuscan wines</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Tuscany is a unique and charming Italian region, that together with a breathtaking landscape, offers exceptional and inimitable flavours. Its wines and food specialties have travelled the world and helped Tuscany in becoming one of the most sought after places to see. We have put together a selection of some of the best wines and food specialties to enjoy and experience the real Tuscany all made by small and passionate producers. Our selection includes the following wines and food specialties:

Chardonnay 
A refreshing white wine, this Chardonnay has a nose of citrus combined with more mature fruits. 

Selverello
A red wine made with Sangiovese grapes. A delicate, balanced and light wine to drink. 

Preziosaterra
A red wine made with mainly Sangiovese plus Merlot and Cabernet Sauvignon grapes slightly oaked with a nose of mature fruits and a spicy notes. 

Chianti Classico 2004 
A fantastic Chianti Classico, complex, with notes of cherries, flowers and spicy hints. 

Chianti Classico Riserva 2003
Another fantastic vintage for this Chianti Riserva, an award winning red wine with a fantastic nose and a wonderful structure. 

Extra virgin olive oil single estate
Tuscan extra virgin olive oil, single estate cold pressed with hints of hay and olives. Very limited production

Included in the selection, completely free of charge, a box of handmade cantuccini and panforte.
</description>
    <name>Flavour of Tuscany food and wine hamper </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Northern case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Southern case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Centre case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The typical Abruzzean wines in their organic version, the &lt;b&gt;Montepulciano&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;Trebbiano&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Cerasuolo d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt; from one of our preferred producers. Three fantastic wines at a special price saving &amp;pound;5

&lt;b&gt;Montepulciano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt;
A powerful, complex, full bodied red wine, bursting with aromas of black fruit, chocolate and scents of vanilla

&lt;b&gt;Cerasuolo d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt;
A dark, full bodied, rose&amp;rsquo; wine made from 100% Montepulciano grapes, with a fruit driven nose, with scents of cherry and red fruit.

&lt;b&gt;Trebbiano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt;
A full bodied white wine with a gold colour, a full and intense nose with aromas of white fruit and a long ending
</description>
    <name>Organic trio, Jasci &amp; Marchesani - SAVE</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Surprise your mum on Mother's day with this giftwrapped hamper full of Italian delicacies. Treat your mum with a selection of fantastic Italian produces for Mother's day and you will make her day. From a pasta sauce to a artisan made panforte to a bottle of mums' favourite Pinot Grigio delle Venezie, this hamper will remind your mum how lucky she is and you don't even tell her "I love you mum", it is written on the card that comes with it. 
The hamper contains:
Artisan panforte 300gr
Organic Modena Balsamic Vinegar 
Aubergines 280gr
Pasta sauce with olives
Pinot Grigio delle Venezie Dal Cero
Chianti Le Tornaie 
Extra Virgin olive oil from Umbria &amp;ldquo;Il Sincero&amp;rdquo; 125ml

</description>
    <name>"Mamma mia" hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Say your mum how grateful you are on Mother's day with this delicious giftwrapped hamper. This delicious hamper contains some of the mother&amp;rsquo;s favourites, from a Modena balsamic vinegar aged 5years for her salads to a classic medium sweet wine like the Orvieto Abboccato for her nights in. The hamper includes a card that says &amp;ldquo;I love you mum&amp;rdquo;. 
The hamper contains:
Artisan made Cantuccini 300gr
Modena Balsamic Vinegar aged 5 years
Orvieto Abboccato
Preziosaterra, red wine Supertuscany
Trebbiano D&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo, white wine
Artichokes 280gr
Sun dried tomatoes 280gr
DOP Extra virgin olive oil from Umbria Viola 125ml</description>
    <name>"Grazie mamma" hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Tell your mum how much you love her on mother's day with this fantastic giftwrapped hamper full of Italian delicacies. Whether your mum loves or not cooking, this hamper will make her smiling. With plenty of Italian delicacies, from the very  delicate taste of the Artichokes to spread on bruschettas or pasta to the 10 years old Modena Balsamic vinegar for salads, this hamper will make your mum the happiest mum in the world. You don't even tell her "I love you mum", it is written on the card that comes with it. 
The hamper contains:
Asparagus 280gr
Modena Balsamic Vinegar aged 10 years
Artichokes pate 180gr
Sun dried tomatoes pate 180 gr
Chilli pepper 180 gr
DOP extra virgin olive oil from Umbria 250ml
Passito del Casale, dessert wine
Preziosaterra, red wine Supertuscany
Podere Bianchino, Chardonnay from Tuscany
</description>
    <name>"Ti voglio bene mamma" hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Let your mum know how much you love her cooking on Mother's day with the chefs preferred ingredients in a fantastic giftwrapped hamper. For this year Mother&amp;rsquo;s day give your mum something special like our chefs&amp;rsquo; preferred ingredients, all your mum needs to impress family and friends. With DOP extra virgin olive oil from Umbria, Modena balsamic vinegar aged 10 years and two jars of pasta sauce, your mum will be the happiest in town and don&amp;rsquo;t worry about anything else, the hamper includes a  card that says &amp;ldquo;I love you mum&amp;rdquo;. 
The hamper contains:
DOP extra virgin olive oil from Umbria Viola 250ml
Modena balsamic vinegar aged 10 years 
2 jars of pasta sauce</description>
    <name>"Mamma for ever" hamper</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Matching wine and chocolate is a very interesting subject and still work in progress. This tasting will give an introduction on matching wine and chocolate followed by the tasting of 6 Italian wines with 6 different type of chocolate. The tasting will be held in Newcastle and the cost is &amp;pound;35 per person. Places are stricly limited to 30.</description>
    <name>Wine and chocolate -  Wine Tasting</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Refosco dal peduncolo rosso is a red wine typical of the north east of Italy, particularly Friuli and Veneto. This wine has an intense and clean nose showing aromas of blackberry and blueberry and it is slightly herbaceous, full and round in the mouth, with an extra kick of acidity and a bitterly palate. It has a lasting aftertaste.</description>
    <name>Refosco dal Peduncolo, La Braghina</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Taste of Sardinia</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Taste of Piedmont</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Taste of Veneto</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>Taste of Abruzzo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Italyabroad.com is helping St Oswalds to raise money for their activities. Italyabroad.com has put together a mixed case of Italian red and white wine at a special price, including free delivery to UK mainland only, and for each case sold, we will donate &amp;pound;10 to St.Oswalds and for each &amp;pound;1000 raised we will donate additional &amp;pound;1000. We really want to help but we need your help. The mixed case of red and white wine includes 2 bottles for each of the following Italian wines:

Selverello (Tuscany)
An Italian red wine made with Sangiovese grapes from Tuscany. A delicate, balanced and light wine to drink. 

Preziosaterra (Tuscany)
An Italian red wine made with a base Sangiovese grapes from Tuscany slightly oaked and a nose of mature fruits and a spicy note. 

Soave (Veneto)
One of the classic Italian white wines. With a brilliant straw-yellow colour and a bouquet with delicate hints of white fruits. 

Chianti Riserva (Tuscany)
Chianti, one of the most famous Italian red wines in its organic version. This Chianti riserva has a full body with a good structure, a garnet color and a red fruits bouquet. 

Chardonnay (Tuscany)
A refreshing Italian white wine, this Chardonnay has a nose of citrus combined with more mature fruits. 

Valpolicella (Veneto)
A light Italian red wine with a lively bouquet, with floral notes and hints of cherry fruits. 

We reserve the right to substitute a wine of equal or higher value in the event of supply difficulties. </description>
    <name>St Oswalds red and white mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A premium &lt;b&gt;Amarone della Valpolicella Classico&lt;/b&gt;. Obtained from old vines with a very low yield, this &lt;b&gt;Amarone della Valpolicella Classico&lt;/b&gt; has aromas of tar and spices with underlying hints of vanilla and chocolate. On the palate, this Amarome is full, big, elegant and rich, is powerfull, a wine of extraordinary concentration and complexity</description>
    <name>Amarone della Valpolicella Classico, Righetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic red wine, this &lt;b&gt;valpolicella ripasso classico superiore&lt;/b&gt; is made repassing the Valpolicella juice on the skins of the Amarone for a few days to add body and character to the valpolicella wine. This &lt;b&gt;valpolicella ripasso classico superiore&lt;/b&gt; has an elegant bouquet with scents of ripe fruit and cinnamon underlying vanilla hints. On the palate, is warm, full and velvety with a lasting aftertaste</description>
    <name>Valpolicella Ripasso Classico Superiore DOC 2004, Camporeale</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Recioto is the traditional dessert wine of the Valpolicella. This Recioto , made using selected grapes from the Lavarini family, is an unctuous red, with a complex nose with fabulous aromas of chocolate and vanilla that evolves to mature fruit and violet. Full bodied, velvety, warm with gentle tannins and with a lasting fruit finish.</description>
    <name>Recioto della Valpolicella Classico DOC 2003, Camporeale</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another premium &lt;b&gt;Amarone&lt;/b&gt;. Obtained from old vine with a very low yield, this &lt;b&gt;Amarone della Valpolicella Classico&lt;/b&gt; has aromas of tar and spices with underlying hints of vanilla and chocolate. On the palate, the wine is elegant, classy, rich, a wine of extraordinary concentration and complexity and its 15.5% alcohol does not show on the palate at all</description>
    <name>Amarone della Valpolicella Classico 2003, Camporeale (375ml)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another unknown white wine from Friuli and what a lovely wine. With an intense, aromatic but yet, elegant, beautiful floral nose, this dry, medium bodied white wine is refreshing and with a mouth-filling texture and a lasting aftertaste. Produced using 100% organically grown ribolla gialla grapes from vineyards located in Friuli, in the Collio area</description>
    <name>Ribolla Gialla Organic, Coceani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A medium bodied merlot made with organically grown grapes from vineyards located in Friuli, in the Colli Orientali area from the Coceani family. This merlot has an intense nose of roses and is slightly herbaceous. In the mouth is full, harmonious, smooth, with sweet tannins and an enduring aftertaste 
</description>
    <name>Merlot Organic Coceani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This is an example of a well made cabernet franc from vineyards located in Friuli. Cabernet Franc is often used in blends but rarely on its own. This wine, that can be drunk young, with its bursting herby aromas, or laid in the cellar, for a more mature and complex wine,  in the mouth is smooth, with soft tannins and the caractheristic herby flavours and the bittery aftertaste. 
</description>
    <name>Cabernet Franc Organic Coceani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This b&gt;Falanghina&lt;/b&gt; wine, made from 100% falanghina grapes from very old vines is rich on the nose and the palate. It presents tempting aromas of apples and pears with underlying notes of almonds on the nose, it is full but crispy in the mouth, fresh with a nice texture, and a long mineral finish.</description>
    <name>Falanghina, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An elegant, full bodied aglianico made with organically grown grapes from Campania, south of Italy, and aged in small, French oak to add complexity to the wine. This food friendly wine has a bursting nose with dried fruit, spices and vanillas hints. In the mouth is well rounded, smooth, with gentle tannins and a vibrant acidity. 
</description>
    <name>Aglianico Organic, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A very elegant white wine, aged in oak barrels to add complexity and vanilla hints, it has floral and mineral aromas. On the palate, this full bodied wine, is beautifully balanced, with the fruit flavours and the crisp acidity. This wine is made with 100% selected hand picked Fiano grapes</description>
    <name>Fiano Beneventano Organic, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Bonea is the name of the vineyard from which the &lt;b&gt;falanghina&lt;/b&gt; grapes that make this wine come from. Made from selected grapes from very old vines &lt;b&gt;harvested later&lt;/b&gt; as to concentrate the juice, this &lt;b&gt;falanghina&lt;/b&gt;, is a rich, elegant white wine with tempting floral aromas and dried fruit and a subtle mineral finish</description>
    <name>Falanghina di Bonea Organic, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Falanghina Donnalaura is made with 100% selected Falanghina, organically grown grapes, in Campania, in the south of Italy, aged in small oak barrels for 12 months to enrich and add complexity to the wine. This is a very elegant wine that shows floral aromas with a lick of seducing vanilla. In the mouth is full, smooth, with fruity flavours and an impressive length.
</description>
    <name>Falanghina Riserva Organic, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An elegant and intense, bright coloured rose&amp;rsquo; made with 100% &lt;b&gt;aglianico&lt;/b&gt; grapes organically grown, with aromas of berries and roses. Refreshing, lively and with a vibrant flavour.</description>
    <name>Aglianico Rose' Organic, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of Italian red and white wines at a special prices, you &lt;b&gt;save over &amp;pound;20 on the normal price&lt;/b&gt;, including a bottle of extra virgin olive oil from Umbria to dress the barbecue. The case contains the following wines:
2 Cannonau (red, full bodied, Sardinia)
2 Lazio Rosato (rose&amp;rsquo;, Latium)
2 Preziosaterra (red, medium bodied oaked,Tuscany)
2 Soave (white, Veneto)
2 Chardonnay (white, Tuscan)
2 Cuvee di merlot rosato (rose&amp;rsquo;, Veneto)
</description>
    <name>Introductory mixed case - SAVE OVER &amp;pound;20</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Produced from grapes obtained from vineyards located between Siena and Arezzo grown organically, in San Savino, this organic &lt;b&gt;Chianti Colli Aretini Riserva&lt;/b&gt; is made only using the best grapes of &lt;b&gt;Sangiovese&lt;/b&gt; and a small percentage of &lt;b&gt;Cabernet Sauvignon aged&lt;/b&gt; in small barriques. The result is a is a full body &lt;b&gt;Chianti Riserva&lt;/b&gt; with character, that offers very good value for money with a garnet colour, a nose of mature red fruits with hints of vanilla and a good structure</description>
    <name>Chianti Riserva Organic 2003 DOCG Castello di Rapale, Giacomo Marengo</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Many are often lost when buying Italian wines, too many wines and too many producers. At Italyabroad.com we only work with small and passionate producers and we have chosen a selection of red and white wines at a very special price, saving over &amp;pound;30, to introduce you to the wonderful world of Italian wines and guide you through the different techniques used and the different grapes and styles available. Italian wines can pair any meal or be drunk in any occasion and with this case, we want you to start knowing them. Each of the wines chosen represents in some way the region it comes from and when drinking the wine, it will be like sitting outside an Italian bar overlooking the passeggiata. The case contains the following wines:

Selverello Sangiovese (Tuscany, red)
Valpolicella (Veneto, red)
Moscato d&amp;rsquo;Asti (Piedmont, white)
Chardonnay (Tuscany, white)
Montepulciano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo (Abruzzo, Organic, red)
Canernet Franc (Friuli, red)
Pinot grigio delle Venezie (Veneto, white)
Fiano (Campania, Organic, white)
Lazio Rosato ( Latium, rose&amp;rsquo;)
40/60 (Latium, Organic, red)
Soave (Veneto, white)
Refosco del Peduncolo (Veneto, red)</description>
    <name>Discovery Italy mixed case - SAVE OVER &amp;pound;20</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A lively, crisp, delicious prosecco di Valdobbiadene with a fine and lasting perlage, aromatic and fresh with notes of apple, peach and floral hints. Dry, velvety and wonderfully refreshing. Obtained from selected hand picked grapes of prosecco from vineyards located in the heart of the Valdobbiadene DOCG area from the family run winery of La Farra. This Prosecco has been chosen as The Times' favourite Prosecco.</description>
    <name>Prosecco di Valdobbiadene Extra Dry, La Farra</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fresh and elegant, moreish &lt;b&gt;prosecco di Valdobbiadene&lt;/b&gt;  with a fine and lasting perlage obtained from selected grapes of prosecco with scents of apple and peach, harmonic and dry. Obtained from selected grapes of &lt;b&gt;prosecco&lt;/b&gt; from vineyards located in the heart of the Valdobbiadene DOCG area from the family run winery of La Farra, the Times' favourite Prosecco.</description>
    <name>Prosecco di Valdobbiadene Brut, La Farra</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This vibrant and refreshing &lt;b&gt;prosecco di Valdobbiadene&lt;/b&gt;,  obtained from hand picked grapes from vineyards located in the &amp;ldquo;toff&amp;rdquo; area of the Valdobbiadene DOC area from the Nardi family, has a fine and lasting prelate with scents of green apple and peach. Dry, velvety and with lingering aftertaste

</description>
    <name>Prosecco di Valdobbiadene TOFF Extra Dry, La Farra</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A delightfully fresh and bubbly, &lt;b&gt;sparkling rose'&lt;/b&gt; made with prosecco grapes from the Nardi family, with an inviting fruity nose with scents of strawberries and cherries, with an elegant pink colour. Crispy, dry, light in the mouth, refreshing with fruity flavours . Mouthwatering</description>
    <name>Sparkling Prosecco Rose', La Farra</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The &lt;b&gt;muller thurgau&lt;/b&gt; is a grape born from the cross of the Riesling and the Sylvaner, mature early and grow well in cool climates like the Alto Adige and the Egger Ramer&amp;rsquo;s one is a fantastic example of what the terroir can produce. A lightly aromatic white wine, crispy and  fresh, bursting with white fruit and floral aromas, vibrant and full in the mouth</description>
    <name>Muller Thurgau, Egger Ramer</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An outstanding, amazingly round, balanced Gewurztraminer made only from selected grapes from vineyards located in the town of Bolzano from the Alto Adige region in the North East of Italy. Elegant on the nose with aromas of roses, cinnamon and nutmeg; full-bodied but lively, rich and, with a creamy texture and a vibrant dash of acidity, and a long finish. 
</description>
    <name>Gewurztraminer, Egger Ramer</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another example of a fantastic &lt;b&gt;pinot bianco&lt;/b&gt;, this time from Trentino. A clean and elegant white wine, medium bodied with a nose bursting of apples and peaches. Crispy, refreshing and with a lingering finish. Made only from selected grapes </description>
    <name>Pinot Bianco, Egger Ramer</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>With a lively cherry red colour and a distinctly fruity bouquet with hints of cherries and strawberries, this rose&amp;rsquo; wine is made with &lt;b&gt;lagrein&lt;/b&gt; grapes from the Egger Ramer family. Fresh, medium bodied, with a vibrant acidity and an enduring aftertaste with an elegant bitter twist</description>
    <name>Lagrein Rose', Egger Ramer</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This &lt;b&gt;Lagrein&lt;/b&gt; is an excellent interpretation of the grape with a deep ruby colour and a nose of violets and plums with sandalwood scents. Fresh, lively with a clean acidity and smooth sweet tannins. Made with selected grapes from vineyards located in the centre of Bolzano, Gries, from the Egger Ramer family and &lt;b&gt;aged&lt;/b&gt; in large wood. The &lt;b&gt;Lagrein&lt;/b&gt; is a native grape of the Alto Adige
</description>
    <name>Lagrein, Egger Ramer</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with grapes from vineyards located in the best area from which the wine derives the addition &amp;ldquo;classico&amp;rdquo;, this red wine made with &lt;b&gt;Schiava&lt;/b&gt; grapes from the Egger Ramer family, has a nose of red fruits, easy to drink, round and fresh. Sweet tannins and a lingering finish with a almond twist complete the wine</description>
    <name>S.Maddalena Classico, Egger Ramer</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The secret of the Italian cuisine, its success and healthy benefits, derives from the simplicity of its recipes and the quality of its main ingredients that, in the case of pasta, are olive oil, tomatoes and pasta. This pasta sauce is exactly this, except the pasta. Made using only the freshest and most natural ingredients from the green region of Abruzzo, high quality olive oil, ripe tomatoes and olives, without the addition of any preservative, this pasta sauce serves up to 4 people and can be used on its own or as base for more sophisticated sauce. BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</description>
    <name>Olives pasta sauce, Triveri BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The secret of the Italian cuisine, its success and healthy benefits, derives from the simplicity of its recipes and the quality of its main ingredients that, in the case of pasta, are olive oil, tomatoes and pasta. This pasta sauce is exactly this, except the pasta. Made using only the freshest and most natural ingredients from the green region of Abruzzo, high quality olive oil, ripe tomatoes and aubergines, without the addition of any preservative, this pasta sauce serves up to 4 people and can be used on its own or as base for more sophisticated sauce. BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</description>
    <name>Aubergines pasta sauce, Triveri BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made without use of preservatives, this pasta sauce with olives is enough for up to 4 people. Made only using the freshest and most natural ingredients from the green region of Abruzzo, it can be used on its own or as base for more sophisticated sauces. 
</description>
    <name>Basil pasta sauce, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made without use of preservatives, this pasta sauce with olives is enough for up to 4 people. Made only using the freshest and most natural ingredients from the green region of Abruzzo, it can be used on its own or as base for more sophisticated sauces. 
</description>
    <name>Pepper pasta sauce, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic red wine, this &lt;b&gt;valpolicella ripasso&lt;/b&gt; is made repassing the Valpolicella juice on the skins of the Amarone for a few days to add body and character to the Valpolicella wine. This &lt;b&gt;valpolicella ripasso&lt;/b&gt; has an elegant bouquet with scents of ripe fruit and cinnamon underlying vanilla hints. On the palate, is warm, full and velvety with a lasting aftertaste</description>
    <name>Valpolicella Ripasso Classico Superiore DOC 2004 Magnum, Camporeale</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A very special selection of organic wines from different regions and producers with a 30% discount on the normal price... From the everyone favourite Pinot Grigio to the unknow Falanghina, this case boast a wine for every occasion able to pair any meal, from a simple burger to a more complex dishes. The case contains 2 bottles each of the following wines:
Falanghina, Masseria Frattasi (white, Campania)
Cabernet Franc, Coceani (red, Friuli)
Trebbiano d'Abruzzo, Jasci &amp; Marchesani (white, Abruzzo)
Merlot, Coceani (red, Friuli)
Chardonnay, Jasci &amp; Marchesani (white, Abruzzo)
Pinot Grigio, Coceani (white, Abruzzo)</description>
    <name>Organic mixed case - SAVE MORE THAN 20%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Gewurztraminer Egger Ramer (white, Trentino)
Trebbiano d'Abruzzo Jasci &amp; Marchesani(white, Abruzzo)
Prosecco di Valdobbiadene La Farra (sparkling white, Veneto)
Moscato d'Asti Rivetto (white, Piedmont)
Pinot grigio Dal Cero(white, Veneto)
Chardonnay Dal Cero (white, Tuscany)</description>
    <name>Taste of summer white mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Filieri Rosato
Lazio rosato
Aglianico rose
Prosecco rose
Merlot rosato
Lagrein rose
</description>
    <name>Taste of summer rose mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Chianti riserva 
Montepulciano d&amp;rsquo;abruzzo
Valpolicella
Preziosaterra
Aglianico
Cannonau
</description>
    <name>Taste of summer red mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>With our customers&amp;rsquo; favourite wines, this white and red mixed case won&amp;rsquo;t disappoint you and will keep you company during the summer. With award winning wines for every occasion and to pair any dish, you will enjoy a fantastic summer the Italian way. The reds range from the award winning medal Chianti Riserva from Giacomo Marengo to the little-known Refosco del Peduncolo. The whites, leaded by the refreshing Pinot Grigio delle Venezie Dal Cero to a lovely Chardonnay  from Tuscany with 20%  discount on the normal price. 
The case contains the following wines:
Refosco del peduncolo La Braghina (red, Veneto)
Pinot grigio delle Venezie Dal Cero (white, Veneto)
Chianti Riserva 2003, Giacomo Marengo (red, Tuscany)
Bardolino (red, Veneto)
Selverello Dal Cero (red, Tuscany)
Filieri rosato Dorgali (rose&amp;rsquo;, Sardinia)
Pinot chardonnay Dal Cero (sparkling, Veneto)
Lagrein Egger Ramer (red, Trentino)
Lazio rosato Donnardea (rose&amp;rsquo;, Latium)
Filieri rosso  Dorgali (red, Sardinia)
Montepulciano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo Jasci &amp; Marchesani (red, Abruzzo)
Chardonnay Dal Cero (white, Tuscany)
</description>
    <name>Our customers mixed case -SAVE 20%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Sardinia is an Italian island that, due to its location, has kept their traditions, in fact there are very few influences of external cultures visible in their heritage and in their cuisine and at the same time, the island, being isolated by the rest of the world has created a cuisine made with ingredients that were easy to find on the island and where the main elements were fish for the population living along the coast and meat for those living inland. The tasting will feature dishes typical of the Sardinian cuisine accompanied by their most typical and known wines and it will be visible how, the wines perfectly match the food, and will also showcase, the only Cannonau white produced. Cannonau is a red grape, but like any red grape, can also be made white. At the moment Cantina di Dorgali is the only producer that does it and it very interesting to taste the same grape and see the difference made by leaving the juice with the skins and stalks.
Menu
On arrival Vermentino di Sardegna

Starter
Wine Filieri Rosato Cannonau White
Antipasto sardo
or
Fregala cozze e gamberi

Main 
Wine Cannonau Vigna di Isalle
Gnocchi alla sarda
or
Spezzatino agnello piu&amp;rsquo; contorno

To finish
Glass of Grappa di Cannoanu aged

The tasting will be held at Sabatini restaurant on the quayside on the 2nd of September starting at 7pm. Places are limited to 25. </description>
    <name>Sardinian wine tasting - Newcastle</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Two fantastic everyday wines made from native Latium grapes at a great price:

&lt;b&gt;Donnardea Colli Albani&lt;/b&gt;
A fantastic dry white wine. Made with native grapes from vineyards surrounding the city of Rome, this dry white wine is slightly aromatic with floral aromas and an enduring aftertaste. Excellent as an aperitif and to accompany light meals

&lt;b&gt;Lazio Rosso&lt;/b&gt;
Made with Sangiovese, Merlot and Cesanese from vineyards surrounding the city of Rome, this medium bodied red wine is round, soft and very smooth on the palate with floral aromas with scents of roses. Wine for all courses
</description>
    <name>Donnardea pair red &amp; white, 2 for &amp;pound;10</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This case contains some of the best examples of Italian wines chosen by our wine experts to lay on your cellar or to drink immediately, spanning from a Pinot noir from Tuscany to a Falanghina from Campania, with a fantastic example of Cannonau riserva, a richly intense Montepulciano D&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo riserva 2000 or the full bodied, harmonius and well rounded Chianti Classico Riserva 2000 and lastly a round, soft and elegant Cabernet Sauvignon from Friuli. We have only 50 cases available so don&amp;rsquo;t delay. This case contains two bottles of each of the wines.

Cannonau di Sardegna DOC Riserva 2004, Cantina di Dorgali 
Pinot Nero Patrizia, Giacomo Marengo
Falanghina del Taburno, Masseria Frattasi
Chianti Classico Riserva 2000, San Pietro
Montepulciano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo riserva 2000, Jasci &amp; Marchesani
Cabernet Sauvignon,Scubla

</description>
    <name>Italyabroad.com premium mixed case - SAVE &amp;pound;40</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Preziosaterra
Fiano Beneventano
Viola Colle Ruita 250ml
3 sughi melanzane pepperoni basilico
pate di funghi 180gr
boscaiola 280gr
carciofi spaccati alla brace
</description>
    <name>Food hamper 1</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Preziosaterra
Fiano Beneventano
Viola Colle Ruita 250ml
3 sughi melanzane pepperoni basilico
pate di funghi 180gr
boscaiola 280gr
carciofi spaccati alla brace
</description>
    <name>Deli hamper 1</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>
Olio viola il sincero 100ml 
Pasta di asparagi
Pasta di pomodori
Pasta di funghi
</description>
    <name>Deli hamper 2</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Aceto balsamico 5 anni
Viola colle ruita 100ml
Sugo melanzane
Pasta di carciofi
Pasta di asparagi
Funghi porcini interi 280gr
</description>
    <name>Deli hamper 3</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Olio viola 750ml 
Chianti classico la casaccia
Aceto balsamico 5 anni
Boscaiola
Asparagi
Sugo al basilico
Pate di pomodori
Pate di funghi
Carciofi spaccati alla brace
</description>
    <name>Deli hamper 4</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Inprivio viola 750ml
Pasta di olive nere
Pomodori secchi
Asparagi
</description>
    <name>Deli hamper 5</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Refosco la Braghina
Soave
Inprivio viola 250gr
Aceto balsamico 5 anni
Sugo alle melanzane
Pate pomodori
Funhi porcini
Asparagi 
</description>
    <name>Deli hamper 6</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Soave
Sugo alle melanzane
Inprivio viola
Olive nere
Olive Verdi marinate
Asparagi 
</description>
    <name>Deli hamper 7</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of delicatessen made by artisans for quick, fresh and healthy appetisers or side dishes and a pasta sauce to be used in the preparation of side dishes or bruschettas and a quick but tastefull pasta. The selection includes a jar each of the following

- Olive Verdi Marinate (Green olives marinated)
- Melanzane (Aubergines)
- Sugo ai peperoni(Pasta sauce with peppers)
- Pomodori Secchi (Sun-dried tomatoes)
- Carciofi Spaccati alla Caterina (Roasted Artichokes)
</description>
    <name>Triveri deli selection</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Together with La Toscana in Newcastle, we have organised a wine tasting night where a selection of wines and matching food will be tasted. The menu includes the following:

&lt;b&gt;On arrival    Soave Dal Cero (Veneto)&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Starter accompanied by Chardonnay Dal Cero (Tuscany)&lt;/b&gt;

Tartina con cipolle rosse e dolcelatte con chutney di pere
(Roast red onion and dolcelatte tart with pear chutney)

&lt;b&gt;Soup accompanied by Falanghina Masseria Frattasi (Campania)&lt;/b&gt;

Zuppa ai funghi di bosco 
(Wild mushrooms soup )

&lt;b&gt;Main course accompanied by Ripasso Coceani (Veneto)&lt;/b&gt;

Stincotto d`agnello 
(Braised minted lamb shanks)

&lt;b&gt;Dessert accompanied by Gocce di Sole Valetti (Veneto)&lt;/b&gt;

Mele e mandorle ricoperte con delle bricciole 
(Apple and almond crumble with Ice cream)

Caff&amp;eacute;

Limoncello

Look forward to seeing you there.
</description>
    <name>Wine tasting event - Newcastle </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The wine tasting includes a 3 courses meal and wines from Campania and Trentino. These two Italian regions are often forgotten but they have very old culinary tradition. We all know the Pizza, but Campania is not just that, whilst, with regard to Trentino, sometime even Italians, don&amp;rsquo;t know much about it. The menu will feature typical dishes of those 2 regions with matching wines and together we will discover these fantastic regions. 
The tasting will be held at The Open Kitchen restaurant in Gosforth, Newcastle. Places are limited to 25 so please book in advance to avoid disappointment
</description>
    <name>Il giro d'Italia october wine tasting</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Together with Foffano in Darlington, we have organised a Tuscan tasting night. The menu includes: 

&lt;b&gt;Starter accompanied by Chardonnay Dal Cero&lt;/b&gt;  

Ribollita 
(Beans and mixed vegetable soup) 

&lt;b&gt;First course accompanied by Sangiovese Dal Cero&lt;/b&gt;

Tagliatelle al cinghiale
(Long egg pasta with wild boar) 

&lt;b&gt;Second course accompanied by Chianti Risalto&lt;/b&gt;

Pollo cacciatora
(Slow cooked chicken supreme in tomato sauce with mushrooms &amp; olives) 

&lt;b&gt;to finish&lt;/b&gt;

Vin Santo &amp; cantuccini
(Almonds biscuits from Siena &amp; Vin Santo)
</description>
    <name>Tuscan night - Darlington </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>From classic and famous Italian wines to unknown, unusual ones, we have selected organic wines that will please every palate and discounted them by 30% for one week only, so hurry up and start your  wine journey through the Italian vineyards&amp;#133; 

The case includes 2 bottles each of the following wines:

&lt;b&gt;Merlot&lt;/b&gt;, Coceani
A medium bodied red wine with an intense nose of roses and slightly herbaceous, full and harmonious in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Trebbiano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt;, Jasci &amp; Marchesani
A full bodied, white wine with a gold colour, a full and intense nose with aromas of white fruit and a long ending

&lt;b&gt;Riesling&lt;/b&gt;, Jasci &amp; Marchesani
An unusual, riesing with an attractive, complex bouquet with floral and tropical aromas and an extra bit of weight that you would expect from grapes grown in a hotter and sunnier climate

&lt;b&gt;Refosco del peduncolo&lt;/b&gt;, Montalbano
A red wine with an intense, ruby red colour and a very good structure with a nose of underwood fruits

&lt;b&gt;Cabernet Franc&lt;/b&gt;, Montalbano
This red wine has an intense colour, inimitable herby aroma, almost of just cut hay, which is aggressive when young but then it grows aristocratic when mature. 

&lt;b&gt;Falanghina&lt;/b&gt;, Masseria frattasi
A full bodied white wine that shows tempting aromas of apples and pears with underlying notes of almonds and a mineral finish



We reserve the right to substitute a product of equal or higher value in the event of supply difficulties. Vintages may vary from those shown.
</description>
    <name>Organic mixed case - 30% OFF</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A special mixed case containing a selection of wines that will please everyone, from the elegant organic Refosco  to a rich falanghina, and the award winning wine Preziosaterra. The cases contains 2 bottles each of the following wines:

&lt;b&gt;Refosco del peduncolo rosso&lt;/b&gt; (Organic, Decanter Bronze winner)
An organic red wine with an intense, red ruby colour with very good structure, underwood fruity scents, sometimes a little bit herby. In the mouth, the wine has a good acidity and a persistent fruit. 

&lt;b&gt;Trebbiano d&amp;rsquo;Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt; (organic)
A full bodied organic Trebbiano d'Abruzzo with a gold colour, a full and intense nose with aromas of white fruit and a long ending. Refreshing and lively with a lovely acid balance

&lt;b&gt;Vermentino&lt;/b&gt;
A vermentino with a light gold colour, with character, light, with an intense, fruity nose with notes of citrus and almonds and a delicate, persistent bouquet. Full-bodied, with medium acidity.

&lt;b&gt;Falanghina&lt;/b&gt;
A white wine with tempting aromas of apples and pears with underlying notes of almonds. Obtained from 100% falanghina grapes from very old vines, this wine is full bodied but crispy and with a nice texture, fresh and with a mineral finish.

&lt;b&gt;Preziosaterra&lt;/b&gt; (IWC and Decanter bronze medal winner)
A blend of Sangiovese, Merlot and Cabernet sauvignon grapes aged for 4 months in new and used oak barrels, this Tuscan red wine has a rich and elegant bouquet of mature fruits, with hints of prunes and cherry, and spicy notes with a touch of vanilla. Medium bodied, soft and round in the mouth.

&lt;b&gt;Selverello&lt;/b&gt;
Made from hand picked Sangiovese grapes this fantastic value wine is fresh, refreshing if drunk at a couple of degree cooler, delightful fragrant with an inviting fruity nose with scents of cherry and spices. Delicate 
in the mouth, balanced and light to taste.

&lt;font size= "-2"&gt;We reserve the right to substitute any of the wine with a similar or more expensive wine&lt;/font&gt;</description>
    <name>Build a dream mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Join us for another entertaining and informative gourmet evening in Sunderland. As usual a selection of Italian wines made by small producers will be paired to a fantastic food prepared by the chefs at Marcellos. The dinner will feature unknown Italian wines and provide information on how to taste wines and what to look for. Each wine will be introduced by a talking about its origin and characteristics. Our events are also a great way to make new friends who share your love for wine. This wine tasting event will have a surprise that will be revealed on the evening 

&lt;CENTER&gt;

Prosecco di Valdobbiadene on arrival

&lt;b&gt;Starter&lt;/b&gt;
Orecchiette pasta wild mushroom and smoked mozzarella paired with Ribolla gialla, Coceani

&lt;b&gt;Main course&lt;/b&gt;
Honey-roast lamb shanks in red wine sauce with Italian mashed potato paired with Chenti, Montalbano

&lt;b&gt;Dessert&lt;/b&gt;
Crostata Ricotta e ricotta e cioccolata paired with Passito 3 Grome, Olivella
 

&lt;/CENTER&gt;


The evening will start at 7.30. Places are limited so reserve your table soon to avoid disappointment. Read one of the latest &lt;b&gt;testimonials&lt;/b&gt; received:

&lt;i&gt;"I have been to over 100 wine tastings all over the world and I would have to say this will stay in my top 10.

Mr. D'Ercole knowledge of wine and about each vineyard was AMAZING!! If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a great night and truly wish to learn about wine this group is one of a kind. From now on this is the only place I will be taking my friends and family.

Thanks again Mr. D'Ercole for an amazing night and I look forward to each month learning more at your event."&lt;/i&gt;(Charles W Denney II)

For more testimonials click &lt;a href="http://www.italyabroad.com/site/base/testimonial"&gt;&lt;font color="#0000FF"&gt; here &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.
</description>
    <name>Wine tasting event- Sunderland</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Join us for an evening of fantastic wines made by small Italian producers and delicious food at Luigis, Harrogate. The theme of the evening is Latium, the native region of Luigi, and will celebrate a region full of fantastic food and wine. Each wine will be introduced by a talking about its origin and characteristics and how to taste and what to look for when drinking wines in general 

&lt;div align="center"&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Menu&lt;/b&gt;

Rice Croquette paired with a glass of Organic Frascati Superiore


Aubergines Parmigiana paired with a glass of Lazio Rosato


Pork steak alla Romana paired with a glass of Syrah


Hot poached pears with mascarpone paired with a glass of Passito Organic Tre Grome
&lt;/div&gt;

Places are strictly limited, so book your seat soon to avoid disappointment. The evening will start at 7.30pm and guests are advised to arrive at around 7.00pm. Read one of our latest testimonials:


&lt;i&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have been to over 100 wine tastings all over the world and I would have to say this will stay in my top 10.  

Mr. D'Ercole knowledge of wine and about each vineyard was AMAZING!!  If you're looking for a great night and truly wish to learn about wine this group is one of a kind.  From now on this is the only place I will be taking my friends and family.

Thanks again Mr. D'Ercole for an amazing night and I look forward to each month learning more at your event."

Regards, 

Charles W Denney II
Chief Operation Officer&amp;rdquo; &lt;/i&gt;

For more testimonials click &lt;a href="http://www.italyabroad.com/site/base/testimonial"&gt;&lt;font color="#0000FF"&gt; here &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.
</description>
    <name>Wine Tasting Harrogate</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Vino Nobile di Montepulciano Riserva made from only the best Canaiolo e Prugnolo gentile grapes is a big red for quality, body, structure and particularly price. An elegant wine with a grainy red colour and a delicate, but intense aromas of chocolate, leather' spice, eucalyptus and vanilla. Rich, smooth and full with a lasting finish. The 2001 has been a fantastic vintage for the Montepulciano area and a very limited quantity has been aged longer to produce this fantastic Vino Nobile di Montepulciano Riserva. </description>
    <name>Vino Nobile di Montepulciano 2003 Riserva, Godiolo </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another Tuscan tradition, panforte and vin santo..Our handmade traditional panforte in a Christmas themed box are made by a small bakery, Pasticceria, and our Vin Santo riserva, vintage 1995, of a golden color and honey nose are made for each other and represent a perfect Christmas gift
</description>
    <name>Vin Santo &amp; handmade traditional panforte</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Taste the world-famous Italian nougat cake handmade with almonds, honey and eggs handmade using traditional method and the finest natural ingredients</description>
    <name>Torrone, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Soft Italian nougat cake with almonds, honey and eggs handmade using traditional method and the finest natural ingredients and covered by dark chocolate</description>
    <name>Torrone morbido ricoperto, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Taste the world-famous Italian nougat cake handmade with almonds, honey and eggs handmade using traditional method and the finest natural ingredients elegantly wrapped. BUY ONE AND GET ONE FREE</description>
    <name>Torrone friabile, Antica Torroneria Piemontese </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description></description>
    <name>tartufi dolci</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These sweets are produced using the local hazelnut, the IGP Piemonte Hazelnut (Protected Geographical Identity), also called the &amp;ldquo;sweet and round hazelnut of the Langhe&amp;rdquo; that because of its sweetness, it is considered the best hazelnut variety in Italy immersed and covered by the finest dark chocolate using only natural ingredients</description>
    <name>Nocciole piemonte in dark chocolate, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Handmade white chocolate truffles. This Sweet truffles are produced using the local hazelnut, the IGP Piemonte Hazelnut (Protected Geographical Identity), also called the &amp;ldquo;sweet and round hazelnut of the Langhe&amp;rdquo; that because of its sweetness, it is considered the best hazelnut variety in Italy and the finest chocolate using only natural ingredients</description>
    <name>Tartufi dolci bianchi, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Small soft, Italian nougat cake handmade with almonds, honey and eggs handmade using traditional method and the finest natural ingredients.</description>
    <name>Torroncini morbidi, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Handmade chocolate consisting in two glazed wafers filled with custard cream, chocolate and grappa made using only the finest ingredients</description>
    <name>Albesi alla grappa, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Handmade chocolate consisting in two glazed wafers filled with custard cream, chocolate, and grappa made using only the finest ingredients</description>
    <name>Albesi al rum, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Selection of handmade specialties, from truffles to nougat cake, ffrom chocolate to albesi. The perfecct gift for the chocolate lover.</description>
    <name>Sacchetto delle bonta', Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Handmade chocolate Truffles. This Sweet truffles are produced using the local hazelnut, the IGP Piemonte Hazelnut (Protected Geographical Identity), also called the &amp;ldquo;sweet and round hazelnut of the Langhe&amp;rdquo; that because of its sweetness, it is considered the best hazelnut variety in Italy and the finest dark chocolate using only natural ingredients</description>
    <name>Tartufi dolci, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from cold pressed olives hand picked to ensure that only the best are used to produce this oil and coming from a single estate between the cities of Assisi and Spoleto, this olive oil  is an extra virgin olive oil of green color with a golden, medium fruity flavour and slightly pungent on the finish.</description>
    <name>Italian extra virgin olive oil Tradizionale 500ml, Viola </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of wines to take you through your Christmas dinner chosen by Andrea, from the aperitif to the panettone. This selection contains all wines you will need for your Christmas dinner, from a Prosecco to entertain your guests to a dessert wine to go with your panettone and you will be guaranteed to ensure your guest. The case contains two bottles each of the following wines:


&lt;b&gt;Prosecco di Valdobbiadene La Farra&lt;/b&gt;
To open the dinner. A fresh and elegant, prosecco di Valdobbiadene with a fine and lasting perlage obtained from selected grapes of prosecco with scents of apple and peach, harmonic and dry

&lt;b&gt;Bianco Pomedes Scubla&lt;/b&gt;
A blend of Chardonnay, Tocai Friulano and Reisling Renano, fermented and refined in barriques, elegant and rich, aromatic with aromas of fruits underlying hints of vanilla. Voted best Italian wine of the year by the Association of Italian sommelier

&lt;b&gt;Nobile di Montepulciano 2004, Godiolo&lt;/b&gt;
A fantastic Tuscan wines. An elegant red wine with a grainy red colour and a fine but intense aromas of chocolate, leather' spice and vanilla, rich, smooth and full in the mouth. Exceptional

&lt;b&gt;Barolo Giulin 2004, Rivetto &lt;/b&gt;
Extremely clean and fresh, with tar and berry aromas that follows through to a full-bodied palate with fine tannins. Warm, elegant and smooth for a the king of Italian wines

&lt;b&gt;Verduzzo Friulano Cratis, Scubla&lt;/b&gt;
A rich, elegant, dessert wine made with verduzzo friulano grapes, aged in barrels with an intense amber colour and a nose of acacia honey, nut and hints of vanilla. Annually awarded three glasses from the Gambero Rosso 

&lt;b&gt;Spumante, Dal Cero&lt;/b&gt;
A moreish spumante obtained with Pinot Bianco and Chardonnay grapes,  packed with delicious, soft, floral flavours and a fine perlage that lingers seductively in the mouth
</description>
    <name>Andrea's Christmas wines </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A luxury Christmas hamper, the ultimate wine and food selection to make Christmas a special day, beautifully presented, perfect as a gift or to share on a cold evening with your loved one. 

Included in the hamper are:

Nocciole Piemonte, handmade nuts covered with dark chocolate
Torrone cioccolato, handmade nougat coverei by chocolate
Roasted artichokes in olive oil, 280gr
Pasta sauce
Green olives
Spumante
Handmade panettone
Modena Balsamic vinegar aged 10 year
Barolo 2004 Rivetto
Albesi alla grappa, chocolate filled with grappa
DOP extra virgin olive oil Colle Ruita 500ml</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper "Cortina"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A Christmas hamper full of all necessary to celebrate Christmas the Italian way,  beautifully presented, perfect as a gift or to share on a cold evening with your loved one. Included in the hamper are:

Handmade cantuccini
Handmade panettone
Spumante
Torrone, handmade nougat
</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper "Firenze"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>aceto 10 anni
nocciole
panettone
cantuccini
spumante</description>
    <name>hamper bologna</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A Christmas hamper full of &amp;ldquo;Tuscan &amp;ldquo; temptations perfect as a Christmas gift for a food lover or to share with your loved ones. The hamper includes a selection of Tuscan produces and comes in a beautifully presented hamper. Included in the hamper are:

Chianti Classico 
Torrone, nougat 
Handmade cantuccini in a Christmas box
Handmade chocolate truffles 
Handmade panettone
Spumante
Tuscan extra virgin olive oil
</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper "Tuscany"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A Christmas hamper filled with gourmet delights with a sweet tooth, perfect as a gift or to share on a cold evening with your loved one. The hamper comes in a beautifully presented hamper. Included in the hamper are:

Lagrein rose&amp;rsquo;
Handmade Panettone
Spumante
DOP Extra virgin olive oil &amp;ldquo;Colleruita&amp;rdquo; 250ml
Handmade cantuccini
Albesi al rhum, chocolate filled with rhum
</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper "Alba"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A Christmas hamper beautifully presented and with something for everyone, perfect as a gift or to share on a cold evening with your loved one. Included in the hamper are:

Handmade panettone
Handmade chocolate truffles
Preziosaterra, Supertuscany red wine
Spumante
Green olives in olive oil 280gr
Viola extra virgin olive oil 125ml
Pasta sauce
</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper "Torino"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Box tartufi
Nocciole
Aceto 10 anni
pinot grigio
Panettone 
colle ruita 500ml</description>
    <name>Christmas hamper "Verona"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A mixed case containing a selection of typical Trentino wines. The wines, unique in their style and very different from all other Italian wines, are all made by the Egger Ramer family, and include 2 bottles each of:

&lt;b&gt;Pinot bianco&lt;/b&gt;
A clean and elegant pinot bianco, medium bodied with a nose bursting of apples and peaches. Crispy, refreshing and with a lingering finish

&lt;b&gt;Gew&amp;uuml;rztraminer&lt;/b&gt; 
An outstanding, wonderfully round and balanced Gewurztraminer. Minerally and elegant on the nose with aromas of roses with cinnamon and nutmeg

&lt;b&gt;Lagrein&lt;/b&gt; 
This Lagrein is an excellent interpretation of the grape with a deep ruby colour with a nose of violets and plums with sandalwood scents

&lt;b&gt;Lagrein rose&amp;rsquo;&lt;/b&gt;
A fresh, medium bodied, fruity rose' wine made with lagrein grapes with a vibrant acidity and an enduring aftertaste with an elegant bitter twist

&lt;b&gt;Muller Thurgau&lt;/b&gt;
A lightly aromatic white wine, this muller thurgau is crispy and fresh, bursting with white fruit and floral aromas, vibrant and full in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Santa maddalena&lt;/b&gt;
A red wine made with the native Schiava grape with a nose of red fruits, easy to drink, round and fresh. Sweet tannins and a lingering finish with a almond twist complete the wine 
</description>
    <name>Trentino mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A mixed case containing a selection of typical Trentino wines. The wines, unique in their style and very different from all other Italian wines, are all made by the Egger Ramer family, and include 1 bottles each of:

&lt;b&gt;Pinot bianco&lt;/b&gt;
A clean and elegant pinot bianco, medium bodied with a nose bursting of apples and peaches. Crispy, refreshing and with a lingering finish

&lt;b&gt;Gew&amp;uuml;rztraminer&lt;/b&gt; 
An outstanding, wonderfully round and balanced Gewurztraminer. Minerally and elegant on the nose with aromas of roses with cinnamon and nutmeg

&lt;b&gt;Lagrein&lt;/b&gt; 
This Lagrein is an excellent interpretation of the grape with a deep ruby colour with a nose of violets and plums with sandalwood scents

&lt;b&gt;Lagrein rose&amp;rsquo;&lt;/b&gt;
A fresh, medium bodied, fruity rose' wine made with lagrein grapes with a vibrant acidity and an enduring aftertaste with an elegant bitter twist

&lt;b&gt;Muller Thurgau&lt;/b&gt;
A lightly aromatic white wine, this muller thurgau is crispy and fresh, bursting with white fruit and floral aromas, vibrant and full in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Santa Maddalena&lt;/b&gt;
A red wine made with the native Schiava grape with a nose of red fruits, easy to drink, round and fresh. Sweet tannins and a lingering finish with a almond twist complete the wine 
</description>
    <name>Trentino mixed case (case of 6)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Taste the wines of Sardinia and the wines that the cannonau and vermentino grapes can produce when vinified by skilled winemakers. Discover the versatility of the cannonau grape, that can produce outstanding white and rose&amp;rsquo; wines together with the classic reds, and elegant, aged red wines. The mixed case contains:

2 &lt;b&gt;Vermentino&lt;/b&gt;
A vermentino with character, with an intense, fruity nose with notes of citrus and almonds and a delicate, persistent bouquet

2 &lt;b&gt;Calaluna&lt;/b&gt;
A white wine made with a red grape that is a revelation. Made with cannonau, this white wine is refreshing and elegant with a delicate nose and a full palate with nutty and honeyed characters

3 &lt;b&gt;Filieri rosato&lt;/b&gt;
An elegant, medium bodied, salmon coloured rose&amp;rsquo; made with cannonau grapes with a delicate and inviting fruity bouquet and an enduring aftertaste

4 &lt;b&gt;Filieri rosso&lt;/b&gt;
A full bodied cannonau bursting with aromas of ripe fruit and plums. Round, soft and very smooth on the palate.

1 &lt;b&gt;Viniola&lt;/b&gt;
A fantastic cannonau riserva, elegant and classy, warm and well balanced bursting with aromas of violets and blackberries with underlying hints of vanilla.</description>
    <name>Sardinia mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Discover why Campania had earned plenty of respect in the wine industry, why their white wines are often compared to the best white wines in the world and the elegance of their red wines. The case contains 2 bottles each of the following wines:

&lt;b&gt;Falanghina&lt;/b&gt;
A full bodied Falanghina that shows tempting aromas of apples and pears with underlying notes of almonds and a mineral finish

&lt;b&gt;Fiano&lt;/b&gt;
A very elegant, full bodied, classy Fiano with floral and mineral aromas beautifully balanced 

&lt;b&gt;Aglianico&lt;/b&gt;
An elegant, full bodied aglianico bursting with dried fruit character aged in French oak to add spicy, creamy hints</description>
    <name>Campania mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Discover some of the finest Tuscan wines from small, passionate producers. Discover the beauty and variety of wines from Tuscany and the wonders of the Sangiovese grapes that produces some of the best and most famous wines in the world. The case contains 2 bottles each of the following wines:

&lt;b&gt;Chianti classico&lt;/b&gt;
A fantastic red wine, a complex Chianti Classico with notes of cherries, flowers and spicy hints

&lt;b&gt;Chianti classico riserva&lt;/b&gt;
This Chianti Classico Riserva has a complex nose with notes of berries and a lick of vanilla, well balanced, round, elegant in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Selverello&lt;/b&gt;
A refreshing red wine made with Sangiovese, delightful fragrant and with an inviting nose of cherry and spices

&lt;b&gt;Chardonnay&lt;/b&gt;
A chardonnay with aromas of citrus combined with more mature fruit, peach and pear, and a lovely fruit acid balance in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Preziosaterra&lt;/b&gt;
A medium bodied red wine, aged, blend of Sangiovese, Merlot and Cabernet sauvignon with a rich and elegant bouquet of mature fruits and spicy notes with a touch of vanilla.

&lt;b&gt;Nobile di montepulciano&lt;/b&gt;
An elegant Vino Nobile di Montepulciano with a grainy red colour and a fine but intense aromas of chocolate, leather' spice and vanilla, rich, smooth and full in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Extra virgin olive oil Dal Cero&lt;/b&gt;
Extra virgin olive oil from Tuscany, from a single estate, cold pressed with hints of hay and olives. Very limited production

&lt;b&gt;Handmade Cantuccini&lt;/b&gt;
A crunchy artisan made cantuccini with whole almonds made with only natural ingredients in a in a nice box</description>
    <name>Tuscany mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Discover some of the finest Tuscan wines from small, passionate producers. Discover the beauty and variety of wines from Tuscany and the wonders of the Sangiovese grapes that produces some of the best and most famous wines in the world. The case contains 1 bottles each of the following wines:

&lt;b&gt;Chianti classico&lt;/b&gt;
A fantastic red wine, a complex Chianti Classico with notes of cherries, flowers and spicy hints

&lt;b&gt;Chianti classico riserva&lt;/b&gt;
This Chianti Classico Riserva has a complex nose with notes of berries and a lick of vanilla, well balanced, round, elegant in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Selverello&lt;/b&gt;
A refreshing red wine made with Sangiovese, delightful fragrant and with an inviting nose of cherry and spices

&lt;b&gt;Chardonnay&lt;/b&gt;
A chardonnay with aromas of citrus combined with more mature fruit, peach and pear, and a lovely fruit acid balance in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Preziosaterra&lt;/b&gt;
A medium bodied red wine, aged, blend of Sangiovese, Merlot and Cabernet sauvignon with a rich and elegant bouquet of mature fruits and spicy notes with a touch of vanilla.

&lt;b&gt;Nobile di montepulciano&lt;/b&gt;
An elegant Vino Nobile di Montepulciano with a grainy red colour and a fine but intense aromas of chocolate, leather' spice and vanilla, rich, smooth and full in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Extra virgin olive oil Dal Cero&lt;/b&gt;
Extra virgin olive oil from Tuscany, from a single estate, cold pressed with hints of hay and olives. Very limited production

&lt;b&gt;Handmade Cantuccini&lt;/b&gt;
A crunchy artisan made cantuccini with whole almonds made with only natural ingredients in a in a nice box</description>
    <name>Tuscany mixed case (case of 6)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A sparkling rose' wine and a box of handmade chocolate to share with your loved one on Valentine night</description>
    <name>Valentine hamper "for ever"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Handmade chocolate with a bottle of rose' sparkling wine for your romantic Valentine evening</description>
    <name>Valentine gifts "only you"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>White handmade truffle chocolate with a sparkling rose' wine to celebrate your loved one</description>
    <name>Valentine hamper "Romeo &amp; Juliette"</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Join us and learn about wine with us. This first class will give you an introduction about wine and plenty of wines to taste. The evening will include the tasting of 6 different wines accompanied by a buffet. Amongst the wine on tasting, we will discover how a red grape can be made white, rose&amp;rsquo; and red wine and their differences. Places are limited to 40. The event will be held at La Toscana in Newcastle and will start at 7.00pm.</description>
    <name>Wine school - introduction to wine</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>&lt;br&gt;Discover the fantastic world of Italian wines made by passionate small producers, taste 10 of the best Italian wines in this journey through Italy and its vineyards. A full afternoon of hidden gems. The afternoon will be held in Leeds, the location will be confirmed close to the date, and places are strictly limited, so hurry up. The selection will include wines from different regions and style and will give you an insight on the wine making process.</description>
    <name>Leeds Wine Tasting </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A powerful, complex, organic, full bodied red wine obtained from hand picked, selected, &lt;b&gt;Montepulciano d'Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt; grapes from vineyards located in Abruzzo and aged for 6 months in oak barrels to give a subtle, well balanced richness. Bursting with aromas of black fruit, chocolate and scents of vanilla, this wine has fine tannins and a fruity, lasting finish</description>
    <name>Montepulciano d Abruzzo Organic,Jasci &amp; Marchesani (375ml)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A full bodied organic &lt;b&gt;Trebbiano d'Abruzzo&lt;/b&gt; with a gold colour, a full and intense nose with aromas of white fruit and a long ending. Refreshing and lively with a lovely acid balance</description>
    <name>Trebbiano d Abruzzo Organic Jasci &amp; Marchesani (375ml)</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The latest addition to the Jasci wines. A native Italian grapes grown in Abruzzo, this white wine will surprise you. With a rich but delicate fruity nose  with a dry palate with peach and bittery almond flavours. A wine worth to be tried 
</description>
    <name>Pecorino, Jasci &amp; Marchesani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This case include all wine you need to host a wine tasting night at your home with your friends. The wine, a bottle of each, will be enough for 12 people. 

Cannonau Bianco
Ribolla Gialla
Falanghina
Refosco del peduncolo rosso
Cabernet Franc
Montepulciano d'Abruzzo Riserva 2001

and you will also receive a selection of tapas (3 jars) to go with the wine completely free.</description>
    <name>Tasting mixed case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>the case include 

Refosco del peduncolo rosso
Cabernet franc
chenti
riesling
chardonnay
cerasuolo</description>
    <name>Organic taste mixed case - SAVE MORE THAN 20%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Another great wine from the Dal Cero family this pinot grigio blush. An easy to drink, and yet, fantastic, rose&amp;rsquo; wine. A Pinot grigio vinified according the tradition in vogue in the, once, Republic of Venice, where the juice remain in contact with the skins for about 12 hours giving the wine its particular coppery color. This rose' wine has a surprising and enchanting fruity bouquet with peach, apricot and strawberries above all. In the mouth is elegant, clean, refreshing, fruity with a clear melon flavour and a bittery finish with a never ending aftertaste making you begging for more</description>
    <name>Pinot Grigio Blush, Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A bright, lively, rose&amp;rsquo; characterise this elegant wine made with Sangiovese. Light, full of freshness and fruity aromas with notes of yellow peach reminding of the Italian summer. Medium bodies, refreshing, vibrant with lasting fruity flavours and a kick of acidity that will make it the perfect wine for tomatoes based dishes.</description>
    <name>Sangiovese rose', Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A white wine of a pale straw color, and a rich, overwhelming floral and fruity bouquet with notes of pear, slightly over riped, nearly sweet. In the mouth is refreshing, clean, light, with fruity flavours and a long aftertaste. An everyday white wine offering fantastic value for money. It can pair light courses, fish and white meat. </description>
    <name>Presuntuoso Bianco, Italyabroad.com</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with 100% Sangiovese grapes grown in Cortona, Tuscany, this everyday red wine offers fantastic value for money. It has a ruby red color and an intense, fruity nose with black cherries and sweet spices. Vinous, smooth and round in the mouth, it is clean and light, with soft tannins. This is the everyday red wine for the Italians; it can pair light courses, pizzas and pasta. </description>
    <name>Presuntuoso Rosso, Italyabroad.com</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The ideal mixed case for your week end containing wines that can pair any food and weather at a fantastic price.. the case contains 2 each of the following wines:

&lt;b&gt;Vermentino&lt;/b&gt;
A white wine with character, with an intense, fruity bouquet with notes of citrus and almonds and a delicate, persistent aftertaste

&lt;b&gt;Chardonnay Tuscany&lt;/b&gt;
A light bodied, delicate white wine with aromas of citrus combined with more mature fruit, peach and pear, and a lovely fruit acid balance in the mouth

&lt;b&gt;Falanghina&lt;/b&gt;
A full bodied white wine that shows tempting aromas of apples and pears with underlying notes of almonds and a mineral finish

&lt;b&gt;Soave&lt;/b&gt;
A refreshing, vibrant white wine with aromas of white fruits and a full palate, with the characteristic final kick of almonds

&lt;b&gt;Selverello&lt;/b&gt;
A refreshing, light red wine made with Sangiovese, delightful fragrant and with an inviting nose of cherry and spices

&lt;b&gt;Preziosaterra&lt;/b&gt;
A medium bodied red wine, aged, a blend of Sangiovese, Merlot and Cabernet Sauvignon with a rich and elegant bouquet of mature fruits and spicy notes with a touch of vanilla</description>
    <name>Week end mixed case - SAVE MORE THAN 30%</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A medium bodied &lt;b&gt;merlot&lt;/b&gt; made with organically grown grapes, completely sulfite free wine, safe to drink for wine lovers with allergies and asthma, from vineyards located in Friuli from the Coceani family. This red wine has an an intense nose of roses, slightly herby. In the mouth is full, harmonious, smooth with soft tannin and an enduring aftertaste. Probably the only totally sulfite free wine available in the UK.</description>
    <name>Merlot Sulfite Free, Coceani</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with a blend of high quality coffee beans, this coffee is the coffee we drink in our offices and houses, the perfect coffee for a proper, real, Italian espresso and you know how important is for us italian, a proper espresso</description>
    <name>Coffee Espresso Italiano</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A proper Gavi Gavi di Gavi , fantastic from a small estate located right in the most vocated area. Obtained from selected hand picked Cortese grapes, this wine is the perfect example of a Gavi wine. Fresh, light, with a fruity nose with recognisable apple hints, with a good acidity in the mouth, plenty of flavour and never ending mineral finish. </description>
    <name>Gavi di Gavi, I Moncalvi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Why not join us for our first wine tasting evening in Seaham. A selection of Italian wines made by small producers will be paired to a fantastic food prepared by the chefs at Classico. The dinner will feature unknown Italian wines and tell how to taste wines and what to look for. Each wine will then be introduced by a talking about its origin and characteristics. Our events are also a great way to make new friends who share your love for wine.

&lt;div align="center"&gt;              
                            &lt;b&gt;Menu&lt;/b&gt;

On arrival &lt;b&gt; Cannonau Bianco &lt;/b&gt;, Cantina di Dorgali

                            &lt;b&gt;Starter&lt;/b&gt;

Crepe Parcels filled with Ricotta &amp; Spinach paired with &lt;b&gt;Tuscan Organic Ribolla &lt;/b&gt;, Coceani

                           &lt;b&gt;Main course&lt;/b&gt;

Roasted Pork Loin stuffed with Apricots. Served with Bacon, Glazed Onions &amp; Pomme Duchesse paired with &lt;b&gt; Cabernet franc &lt;/b&gt;, Scubla

                            &lt;b&gt;Dessert&lt;/b&gt;

Puff Pastry filled with Apple's &amp; Italian Custard, Served with Vanilla Sauce paired with &lt;b&gt;Recioto di Soave&lt;/b&gt;, Dal Cero

&lt;/div&gt;


The evening will start at 7.30. Places are limited so reserve your table soon to avoid disappointment. Read some of the &lt;a href="http://www.italyabroad.com/testimonial"&gt;&lt;font color="#0000FF"&gt; testimonials &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt; received.
</description>
    <name>Wine tasting event- Seaham </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Italian mushrooms pate' is obtained mincing a selection of wild mushrooms and preserving them in olive oil for a rich and full flavour. This pate is perfect for Bruschettas or as ingredient in the preparation of sauces or main courses. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Mushroom pate, Triveri </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made from grapes from a single vineyard, with a very low yield, this white wine has a rich bouquet of flowers and white fruits. In the mouth is fresh, full and with a long aftertaste.</description>
    <name>Coda di Volpe, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with grapes from a single, very old vineyard, with a very low yield, manually harvested, this white wine has an intense and rich fruity and floral nose with hints of apricots and honey, slightly mineral. In the mouth is full and silky with a never ending finish.</description>
    <name>Greco, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This dessert wine is made with grapes from a 120 years old vineyards, located at 800 m above sea level, with a yield of less than 1 kg per vine, dried and then aged for one year in barrique. The result is a wine with a rich nose, with hints of honey and ripe apricot. Full, sweet and long lasting in the mouth. </description>
    <name>Moscato Passito, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Obtained from selected, hand picked, Aglianico grapes, from a vineyard located at about 450 m above sea level and with a yield of less that 1kg per vine. The wine is then aged in barrique for 24 months and refined in the bottle for another 18 months. The result is an outstanding wine with a nose with hints of prunes, tobacco and black fruit. In the mouth is full, thick, velvety with a never ending finish.</description>
    <name>Aglianico Riserva "Iovi Tonant" Organic, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with grapes from a secular vineyard located at about 700 m above sea level, with a yield per vine of less than 1kg and drying the grapes for three months in the open air, this wine is then aged for a total of 4 years in barriques. The result is a red wine with a rich and complex nose with hints of black cherry jam, tobacco, vanilla. In the mouth is structured, smooth, velvety and with a long lasting. This is the first vintage and only 900 bottles were produced. </description>
    <name>Amarone di Aglianico, Masseria Frattasi</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>
Have you ever dreamt of becoming a wine buyer, travelling the world searching for the finest wines, leaving the city life behind? We wants to give you the opportunity of experiencing, first hand, the &amp;ldquo;hard&amp;rdquo; life of a wine buyer, except the travelling, we have already done it for you. We are looking for 40 people to help us to decide which new wines to add to our, already more than 250 wines, portfolio. 

The evening, which will be held at Blackfriars in Newcastle, will give you an insight of what a wine buyer life is. There will be at least 20 wines on tasting and you will be required to taste all of them and to fill a wine card with your comments for every wine, spittoons will be provided in case you really want to act like a proper wine expert. 

The wines on tasting will include the Italian Classic Method Sparkling wine, Franciacorta, and Amarone only to mention a couple. The event is free, however, to avoid places being booked without certainty of being able to attend, we are charging &amp;pound;10 per person which include a bottle of wine worth at least &amp;pound;10 to take home at the end of the evening. 

</description>
    <name>Become a wine expert for one day</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>GRAPE HARVESTING IN TUSCANY, CORTONA
5 days/4 nights (Friday 18th to Tuesday 22nd September )
 
Day 1 &amp;ndash;96 Meeting at Pisa&amp;rsquo;s airport or in Cortona in the afternoon. Welcome drink and special dinner with tasting of different Tuscan wines.

Day 2- Typical Tuscan country breakfast. Morning class &amp;ldquo;Introduction to wine&amp;rdquo;. Lunch and transfer to Cortona for a visit of the town and evening at your disposal.

Day 3 &amp;ndash; After breakfast, transfer to the Dal Cero&amp;rsquo;s vineyards to start the vendemmia (harvesting). Outdoor lunch with Tuscany specialities including prosciutto toscano, porchetta, pecorino toscano and pane toscano. After lunch, possibility of visiting the area or continue harvesting. After the harvesting, return to the winery where you will be shown the equipment and described the wine making process, with taste of the grape juice before, during and after the fermentation. Evening at your disposal

Day 4 &amp;ndash; After breakfast, visit at the &amp;ldquo;Godiolo&amp;rdquo; winery in Montepulciano and at the winery &amp;ldquo;7 Camicie&amp;rdquo; in Montalcino with tasting of different wines and different vintages. In the evening, farewell dinner in Cortona. 

Day 5- Breakfast and departure.


Package include:
&amp;#149; 4 nights accommodations in a B&amp;B in Cortona
&amp;#149; Winery visits and wine tasting as per itinerary
&amp;#149; 4 lunches or dinners (one a day)
&amp;#149; Breakfast daily
&amp;#149; 60 bottles of wine made with your picked-up grapes with personalised label 
&amp;#149; Full-day at disposal

The price is per person, based on double occupancy. Places are limited to 10. 
</description>
    <name>Grape Harvesting In Tuscany, Cortona</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A delicious combination of sun-ripened tomatoes, onion and mushrooms without any preservative, ready to be used. Simply cook your pasta, warm the sauce up in a pan and when the pasta is ready, mix them together, add a few drops of extravirgin olive oil and parmesan cheese. </description>
    <name>Mushrooms Pasta Sauce - Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A delicious combination of sun-ripened tomatoes, onions, peppers, aubergines and courgettes without any preservative. Simply cook your pasta, warm the sauce up in a pan and when the pasta is ready, mix them together, add a few drops of extravirgin olive oil and parmesan cheese. 
</description>
    <name>Ortolana Pasta Sauce - Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A delicious combination of sun-ripened tomatoes, onion and artichokes without any preservative. Simply cook your pasta, warm the sauce up in a pan and when the pasta is ready, mix them together, add a few drops of extravirgin olive oil and parmesan cheese. 
</description>
    <name>Artichokes Pasta Sauce - Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of Italian dried tomatoes, green olives, basil, chilly peppers and cappers minced and preserved in olive oil. This pate is perfect for Bruschettas or as ingredient in the preparation of sauces or main courses. For ideas, visit our recipes section.</description>
    <name>Bruschetta pate, Triveri  </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Make you own arrabbiata pasta, using our ready sauce that follows the authentic recipe. Simply cook your pasta and add the sauce and your arrabbiata is ready.. add extra chilli if you want it really "arrabbiata"</description>
    <name>Arrabbiata pasta sauce</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A selection of mushrooms conserved in only extra virgin olive oil, without any preservative, ideal as a side dish for main courses or to use in the preparation of bruschettas, simply toast the bread and add a couple of spoons of mushrooms
</description>
    <name>Mixed Mushrooms Boscaiola, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Freshly-picked Italian &lt;b&gt;asparagus&lt;/b&gt;, with a very delicate taste, in extra virgin olive oil ideal as a side dish to compliment a main course. The fresh &lt;b&gt;asparagus&lt;/b&gt; are immediately put in extra virgin olive oil to preserve their full flavour. </description>
    <name>Asparagus EV, Triveri</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>ddd</description>
    <name>Peperoncini extra</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>These sun dried Italian tomatoes, obtained leaving the tomatoes drying under the Adriatic sun, have a rich and delicious flavour that is perfect in the preparation of the Italian antipasto or in the preparation of sauces, to give the sauce a more intense flavour. The sun dried tomatoes are immediately put in extra virgin olive oil to preserve their full flavour and do not contains any preservative, are 100% natural. For ideas, visit our recipes section</description>
    <name>Sun dried tomatoes extra</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>An outstanding wine, elegant, full bodied red wine made with Syrah grapes grown in vineyards located in the town of Cortona. The bouquet presents initially notes of ripe fruit, plum, blackberry, blackcurrant, and blueberry and successively shows candied fruit, chocolate, vanilla and toasted hazelnut amongst the others. In the mouth amaze its balance and the great texture and length, indication that the Clanis will develop into a great wine. Presented in a Rhone style bottle, the wine certainly has a lot in common with the best wines of the Northern Rhone. It is recommended to decant the wine before opening. Produced in very limited quantity, the Syrah Clanis, has received a silver medal at the Syrah du Monde 2009, the biggest international competition reserved for wine made with Syrah</description>
    <name>Syrah Clanis, Dal Cero</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>This Bardolino Chiaretto, that translates as light in color Bardolino, is a fantastic rose' wine, medium pink in color with a fruity notes with hints of fresh strawberry and cherry fruit, refreshing, fruity and clean in the mouth.  </description>
    <name>Bardolino Chiaretto, Valetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fresh, crispy, and well balanced dry white wine. This Bianco di Custoza, with a light straw yellow color, has lemon notes softened by apple fruit on the nose. In the mouth is light, with mineral elements and a bittery flavour and a never ending finish. </description>
    <name>Bianco di Custoza, Valetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>I often get asked what are my favourites red wines and I always reply saying that I have many favourites and it depends of what I am having and how I am feeling. Said that, I have put together a selection of red wines that I like. The case contains 1 each of the following wines, , for more information about the wines you can read the tasting notes on their respective page

&lt;b&gt;Nobile di Montepulciano 2004, Godiolo&lt;/b&gt;
Elegant, classy, for when I am sitting on front of the TV with my good friends
&lt;b&gt;Patrizia 2000, Pinot Nero or Noir, Marengo&lt;/b&gt;
For when I want or need to impress
&lt;b&gt;Clanis, Dal Cero&lt;/b&gt;
Elegant, Chchateauneuf du pape style, for when I want to surprise
&lt;b&gt;Aglianico, Masseria Frattasi&lt;/b&gt;
Full, rich, the perfect Italian food companion 
&lt;b&gt;Selverello, Dal Cero&lt;/b&gt;
Simple, essential, the everyday wine
&lt;b&gt;Lagrein, Egger Ramer&lt;/b&gt;
Unusual, unknown, good to show off your wine knowledge
</description>
    <name>Andrea's Red Wines Mixed Case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>I often get asked what are my favourites white wines and I always reply saying that I have many favourites and it depends of what I am having and how I am feeling. Said that, I have put together a selection of white wines that I like. The case contains 1 each of the following wines, for more information about the wines you can read the tasting notes on their respective page

&lt;b&gt;Pomedes, Scubla&lt;/b&gt;
When you have guests that don't like white wines
&lt;b&gt;Falanghina Riserva, Masseria Frattasi&lt;/b&gt;
Rich, full of the Italian sun if you are feeling grey
&lt;b&gt;Sauvignon, Scubla&lt;/b&gt; 
Perfect, to bring excitement on the table
&lt;b&gt;Chardonnay, Dal Cero&lt;/b&gt;
When you have guests that "cannot stand Chardonnay"
&lt;b&gt;Pinot grigio del Collio, Coceani&lt;/b&gt;
For a different Pinot Grigio experience
&lt;b&gt;Gew&amp;uuml;rztraminer, Egger Ramer&lt;/b&gt;
who said that in Italy we dont know how to make a good Gew&amp;uuml;rztraminer</description>
    <name>Andrea's White Wines Mixed Case</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A crunchy, handmade cantuccini, with Chestnuts and Hazelnuts in a nice box. These cantuccini are made with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients. </description>
    <name>Cantuccini with Chestnuts and Hazelnuts</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A crunchy, handmade cantuccini, with raisins in a nice box. These cantuccini are made with 100% natural ingredients, without any artificial flavouring, colourings, preservatives or GM ingredients. Please note that they are addictive. </description>
    <name>Cantuccini with Raisins</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with a single blend of 100% high quality Arabica beans, this coffee is the coffee we drink in our offices and houses, the perfect coffee for a proper, real, Italian espresso and you know how important is for us italian, a proper espresso</description>
    <name>Coffee 100% Arabica  </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with a blend of high quality coffee beans, this coffee is the coffee we drink in our offices and houses, the perfect coffee for a proper, real, Italian espresso and you know how important is for us italian, a proper espresso</description>
    <name>Coffee Gold</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Made with a blend of high quality coffee beans, this coffee is the coffee we drink in our offices and houses, the perfect coffee for a proper, real, Italian espresso only decaf and you know how important is for us italian, a proper espresso</description>
    <name>Coffee Decaf</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Selection of different chocolates and torroni</description>
    <name>Bauletto Assortito, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Italian soft orange flavoured nougat bar handmade with almonds, honey and eggs</description>
    <name>Torrone Orange Flavoured, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Orange flavoured chocolate bar with torrone chips and hazelnut paste covered in pure chocolate</description>
    <name>Chocolate Bar Orange Flavoured, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Chocolate with torrone chips, hazelnut paste and coffee, covered in pure chocolate</description>
    <name>Chocolate Bar Coffee Flavoured, Antica Torroneria Piemontese </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>Italian nougat bar handmade with almonds, honey and eggs, using traditional method and the finest natural ingredients</description>
    <name>Torrone Astuccio, Antica Torroneria Piemontese</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>We are pleased to announce another wine tasting in Newcastle. We would like to invite you to join us at Rocco Bar Trattoria, formerly La Toscana, in 22 Leazes Park Road, Newcastle-upon-Tyne,, Newcastle. The wine tasting will be held in the private room where we will be able to enjoy the food and the wines at our own pace. The tasting, in a form of a buffet, will include plenty of Italian food and 7 different wines, whites, reds and desserts, each one introduced by a talking about its origin and characteristics and how to taste what to look for when drinking wines. Our events are also a great way to make new friends who share your love for wine. Our wine tasting evenings are also a fantastic and much appreciated Christmas gift.

&lt;div align="center"&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Menu&lt;/b&gt;

Garlic bread
Bruschetta al pomodoro
Mixed marinated olives
Small pizzas
Insalata Caprese
Parma ham, Salame, Mortadella 
Lasagna 
Mushrooms Risotto
Cicken and sage polpettine
Roast chicken legs
Continental cheese 
Basket of fresh fruit
Torta della nonna 
Torta alle fragole di bosco

&lt;b&gt;Wines&lt;/b&gt;

Pinot Grigio Collio
Sauvignon 
Ribolla 
Pinot grigio blush
Cabernet franc
Aglianico
Moscato passito

&lt;/div&gt;

Places are limited, book your seat soon to avoid disappointment. The evening will start at 7.30pm and guests are advised to arrive at around 7.00pm. Read our latest testimonials:

&lt;i&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have been to over 100 wine tastings all over the world and I would have to say this will stay in my top 10."&lt;/i&gt;
Charles W Denney II

&lt;i&gt;"Andrea, your knowledge is inspirational! Thank you for a wonderful night - again" &lt;/i&gt;
A Simmons (January 2010)

For more testimonials click &lt;a href="http://www.italyabroad.com/site/base/testimonial"&gt;&lt;font color="#0000FF"&gt; here &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.
</description>
    <name>Newcastle Wine tasting </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>We are pleased to announce another wine tasting in Newcastle. We would like to invite you to join us at Rocco Bar Trattoria, formerly La Toscana, in 22 Leazes Park Road, Newcastle-upon-Tyne,, Newcastle. The wine tasting will be held in the private room where we will be able to enjoy the food and the wines at our own pace. The tasting, in a form of a buffet, will include plenty of delicious Italian food and 7 fantastic Italian wines made by small, passionate producers, a selection of whites, reds and desserts, each one introduced by a talking about its origin and characteristics and how to taste what to look for when drinking wines. Our events are also a great way to make new friends who share your love for wine. Our wine tasting evenings are a fantastic and very appreciated gift.

&lt;div align="center"&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Menu&lt;/b&gt;

Garlic bread
Bruschetta al pomodoro
Mixed marinated olives
Small pizzas
Insalata Caprese
Parma ham, Salame, Mortadella 
Lasagna 
Mushrooms Risotto
Cicken and sage polpettine
Roast chicken legs
Continental cheese 
Basket of fresh fruit
Torta della nonna 
Torta alle fragole di bosco

&lt;b&gt;Wines&lt;/b&gt;

Pinot Grigio Collio
Sauvignon 
Ribolla 
Pinot grigio blush
Cabernet franc
Aglianico
Moscato passito

&lt;/div&gt;

Places are limited, book your seat soon to avoid disappointment. The evening will start at 7.30pm and guests are advised to arrive at around 7.00pm. Read our latest testimonials:

&lt;i&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have been to over 100 wine tastings all over the world and I would have to say this will stay in my top 10."&lt;/i&gt;
Charles W Denney II

&lt;i&gt;"Andrea, your knowledge is inspirational! Thank you for a wonderful night - again" &lt;/i&gt;
A Simmons (January 2010)

For more testimonials click &lt;a href="http://www.italyabroad.com/site/base/testimonial"&gt;&lt;font color="#0000FF"&gt; here &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.
</description>
    <name>Newcastle February Wine tasting </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Franciacorta D.O.C.G. is the Italian sparkling wine made using the classic method with the second fermentation in the bottle and has been fermented for at least 18 months. This Franciacorta has a persistent and fine perlage, a nose with bread and yeast with notes of dried fruit. On the palate is fresh and balanced</description>
    <name>Franciacorta, La Valle</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Franciacorta D.O.C.G. is the Italian sparkling wine made using the classic method with the second fermentation in the bottle. A vintage Franciacorta Riserva made using Chardonnay and Pinot Noir grapes and fermented for at least 60 months to be called "riserva". Tasting notes coming ...</description>
    <name>Franciacorta Regium, La Valle</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Franciacorta D.O.C.G. is the Italian sparkling wine made using the classic method with the second fermentation in the bottle and the "saten" is the blanc de blanc of the Franciacorta, and takes its name from the smoothness of the wine.  This vintage Franciacorta has a very creamy and fine perlage, a delicate nose with floral hints, dried fruit. Rich, fresh and smooth on the palate. Fermented for at least 37 months</description>
    <name>Franciacorta Saten, La Valle </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>The Franciacorta D.O.C.G. is the Italian sparkling wine made using the classic method with the second fermentation in the bottle. This vintage Franciacorta, extra brut, is made using Chardonnay and Pinot Noir grapes and fermented for at least 37 months, from here "millesimato". Tasting notes coming ...</description>
    <name>Franciacorta Naturalis, La Valle </name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic Brunello di Montalcino from one of our preferred producers</description>
    <name>Brunello di Montalcino, Le 7 camicie</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A fantastic Amarone, rich, big, powerful, from a single vineyards located in one of the most vocated area in the Classic area. Tasting notes to follow.</description>
    <name>Amarone della Valpolicella Classico Monteci, Righetti</name>
  </product>
  <product>
    <description>A unique dessert wine, the Barolo Chinato derives from an ancient recipe. The aged Barolo is infused with aromatic herbs.  Its spicy, intense and persistent nose and the bittersweet taste make it a fantastic wine. Not just a meditation wine, the Barolo Chinato is a fantastic companion with chocolate desserts.
</description>
    <name>Barolo Chinato, Rivetto</name>
  </product>
</products>
